<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<response>

<lst name="responseHeader">
  <int name="status">0</int>
  <int name="QTime">2</int>
  <lst name="params">
    <str name="q">headline:terrorist</str>
    <str name="indent">true</str>
    <str name="sort">date desc</str>
    <str name="rows">2147483647</str>
    <str name="wt">xml</str>
  </lst>
</lst>
<result name="response" numFound="232" start="0">
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Drill planned to simulate terrorist attacks on buses</str>
    <str name="body">In the wake of the terrorist attacks in Paris, operators of the Taipei Joint Bus System and the Taipei City Government’s Police Department on Friday next week are to stage an antiterrorism drill simulating an attack on the bus system, an operator said yesterday. The drill is to include practice calming passengers, negotiating with terrorists and carrying out a counterterrorism raid, Metropolitan Transport Corp head Hung Tsang-lang (洪滄浪) said. The aim is to train police and other personnel, and increase public awareness of possible terrorism, Hung said. The drill is gaining extra attention amid fears that Taiwan could become a target of the Islamic State after the national flag appeared in a propaganda video made by the group. The flag was among the banners of 60 other nations that appeared in the video and was displayed next to the US flag. Awareness of antiterrorism measures in Taiwan was heightened after US President Barack Obama named Taiwan as part of an Asia-Pacific coalition against the Islamic State during the ASEAN East Asia summit in Kuala Lumpur on Nov. 22. Hung said that bus companies in Taipei have regularly staged such drills over the past few years. The preparatory work for this year’s drill started four months ago, prior to the terrorist attacks in Paris last month, Hung said. The drill is set to be staged at a station in Neihu District (內湖), with the participation of about 60 people, including more than 20 special forces personnel. Buses, firefighting vehicles, ambulances and police vehicles are to be deployed for the drill, Hung said. Specialized weapons will be carried during the drill, Hung added.</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/taiwan/archives/2015/12/09/2003634391</str>
    <str name="source">taiwan</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'You Ain't No Muslim, Bruv': Britons Defiant Over 'Terrorist' Knife Attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/you-aint-no-muslim-bruv-britons-defiant-over-terrorist-knife-attack-1252199</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UK Police Charge Man Over 'Terrorist Incident' At London Metro Station</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/uk-police-charge-man-over-terrorist-incident-at-london-metro-station-1252161</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">UK</str>
    <str name="longitude">-2.212511778</str>
    <str name="lattitude">54.56088638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Barack Obama in Speech to Nation Vows to Defeat 'New Phase' of Terrorist Threat</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/barack-obama-in-speech-to-nation-vows-to-defeat-new-phase-of-terrorist-threat-1251845</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">INTERVIEW: Terrorist attacks in Taiwan a possibility, expert says</str>
    <str name="body">Liberty Times (LT): From the Sept. 11, 2001, terror attacks to the Islamic State (IS) group’s recent attacks in France, are international terrorist attacks changing into something new? Are new trends emerging? Wang Yu-wei (汪毓瑋): Yes. 9/11 is the watershed between old and new terrorism. Older forms of terrorism, such as that of the Irish Republican Army or Spanish ETA [Euskadi Ta Askatasuna, or Basque Country and Freedom, an armed group of the Basque National Liberation Movement], have objectives such as the independence of Northern Ireland or the Basque regions. If they can enter a reasonable and equitable political process with the government, they are willing to negotiate or even make compromises. However, new terrorist organizations, which include al-Qaeda and the IS, wish to build a Sharia state spanning from the Mediterranean to Southeast Asia, that is distinct from existing Muslim-ruled states, such as Saudi Arabia or Indonesia. In the eyes of IS, Saudi Arabia had already absorbed essential qualities of Western democracy, and is therefore a “secular regime.” Older terrorist [organizations] needed to negotiate with the government, and could not use tactics that are excessively cruel or cause too many civilian casualties. Primarily they attacked targets of symbolic value to the state apparatus, such as military personnel, law enforcement, court and civil government officials. Though new terrorists also attack targets that are symbolic of the state apparatus, they do not care about civilians and they even think that attacks on civilians can coerce governments into making concessions or surrender. Causing maximum casualties is their most important objective and therefore they use deliberately cruel tactics to kill as many people as possible and the more people there are in an area, the more likely it will be chosen as a target. [To them] those are necessary sacrifices in a jihad to achieve victory. LT: The US, Russia, France and Germany appear to be joining efforts to fight the IS. What kind of tactics do you think they will use to strike back? How will the situation develop? Wang: The international response includes airstrikes to degrade IS combat capabilities and retaking oil fields, dams, towns and cities. The softer approach is counter-radicalization. The IS has depended on “push” and “pull” to replenish its numbers. Pull refers to using mosques, jails and the Internet to spread its ideologies and ideas for the purpose of convincing recruits to join it; push refers to the conditions of social injustice and unequal distribution of resources that become an invisible force pushing those who felt uncared for [by society] to the organization. Al-Qaeda and the IS are skillful in building narratives. Therefore, counter-radicalization uses television stations, non-governmental organizations and various activities to publicize the IS narrative. It must be noted that the IS believes in an ultimate war between the Orient and the Occident, a return to the irreconcilable conflict during the age of the Crusades. However, radical Muslims are a minority. They need to recruit moderate Muslims into their organization through [the mechanism of] outrage. Therefore, they use incessant attacks to elicit reaction from nations that were attacked, to facilitate its Internet propaganda campaign: “I am oppressed by Western states because I fight for the ideals and the future of Muslims. You must rise up to fight by our side.”</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/taiwan/archives/2015/12/07/2003634227</str>
    <str name="source">taiwan</str>
    <str name="location">Taiwan</str>
    <str name="longitude">120.960515</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.69781</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">London Tube Stabbings 'Terrorist Incident': Police</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/anti-terror-police-probe-london-tube-knife-attacks-1251517</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">London</str>
    <str name="longitude">-0.127758</str>
    <str name="lattitude">51.507351</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Knife Attacker Slashes Man in London 'Terrorist Incident'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/knife-attacker-slashes-man-in-london-terrorist-incident-1251745</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">London</str>
    <str name="longitude">-0.127758</str>
    <str name="lattitude">51.507351</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">My father is a revolutionary, not terrorist: Chetia daughter</str>
    <str name="body">Guwahati: Life has come full circle for Ulfa founding general secretary Golap Baruah alias Anup Chetia's 20-year-old daughter Bonnya Boruah. She lived with the fake identity of Bannya Akhtar in Dhaka since she was just over two years. A 4th-semester commerce student in Bangalore, Bonnya now lives with her real identity with freedom. She has promised herself not to go back to her past life. The life of Bonnya, who nurses an ambition to work for making Assam an economically independent and developed state, is a story of a child of a militant leader, who had learnt to live life on the run before she even started going to school. I don't want to relive that life again. Whatever I do now, I will do it with pride and in an open world. I have told my mother, too, that we are not going to live on the run again, said Bonnya. Bonnya and her elder brother, Sagar Baruah alias Islam, went to schools in Dhaka on fake identities along with Paresh Baruah's two children Ankur and Akash besides Baruah's adopted son Anik. We had our share of our childhood in our own way. Paresh uncle would take five of us to rural areas outside Dhaka. We enjoyed those days, she added. She said, Initially, when I went to Bangalore to study, my friends did not know about me and my father. But now life has become difficult as they call me a terrorist's daughter. I remain silent but I know my father is not a terrorist but a revolutionary and I love him, she said here after she met her father at Guwahati jail. She added that she now understands that her father and others are fighting for Assam's sovereignty. I have learnt from people that what my father is leading has disadvantages. His struggle is not without mistakes but then history tells us that every freedom struggle has had collateral damages.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/guwahati/My-father-is-a-revolutionary-not-terrorist-Chetia-daughter/articleshow/50063986.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Paris attacks: Suspect terrorist visited UK earlier this year</str>
    <str name="body">LONDON: One of the terrorists who was involved in the 13/11 carnage in Paris had visited two cities in the United Kingdom earlier this year to meet other terror suspects. The Guardian reports that the unnamed terrorist managed to visit London and Birmingham before slipping away to Europe even though there was a terror alert. During his visit, he met with other terror suspects with the intention of plotting or assisting terrorist activity against the UK. The terrorist then later became part of the serial attacks in Paris which plunged France into its biggest national security crisis since the Second World War. The suspects he visited in UK are under investigation by MI5 and police counter-terrorism units. A total of 11 terrorists were behind the attacks on Paris, which were carried out three weeks ago of which nine are dead and two are still loose.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/europe/Paris-attacks-Suspect-terrorist-visited-UK-earlier-this-year/articleshow/50052840.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Suspected Hizbul Mujahideen Terrorist Arrested in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/suspected-hizbul-mujahideen-terrorist-arrested-in-kashmir-1249983</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-12-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">India, US Agree to Sign Pact on Sharing Terrorist Watch-List Information</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/india-us-agree-to-sign-pact-on-sharing-terrorist-watch-list-information-1250309</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">India US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-116.215562</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.720577</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">No known terrorist threat to Rio Olympics: Official</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//sports/more-sports/others/No-known-terrorist-threat-to-Rio-Olympics-Official/articleshow/49957225.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Rio</str>
    <str name="longitude">-43.172896</str>
    <str name="lattitude">-22.906847</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">No known terrorist threat to Rio Olympics: Official</str>
    <str name="body">BRASILIA: Brazil is preparing to deal with a terrorist attack at the Rio Olympics but has no information of any planned plots, the country's intelligence chief told AFP on Friday. "We have no information about a terrorist cell preparing in Brazil. Our risk assessment does not indicate this, but we are working permanently as if the threat were imminent, as if this could happen tomorrow," Wilson Trezza, director of the Brazilian Intelligence Agency, said. With nine months before the first Summer Games in South America, Brazilian security officials say they will be able to stop any threat. Fears have risen since the attacks two weeks ago in Paris, including outside the national football stadium, that left at least 130 people dead. Brazil is working so as "not to be taken by surprise," Trezza said at a seminar in the capital Brasilia. Brazil has no history of conflict with Islamist or other violent radical groups. However, with 10,500 athletes from 206 countries and dozens of heads of state and large numbers of tourists, the Olympics are considered a potential target. Brazil says it will deploy 85,000 security personnel, double the number used during the 2012 London Olympics. "It will be the biggest integrated security operation in the history of Brazil," said Sports Minister George Hilton.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//sports/more-sports/others/No-known-terrorist-threat-to-Rio-Olympics-Official/articleshow/49957225.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Rio</str>
    <str name="longitude">-43.172896</str>
    <str name="lattitude">-22.906847</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Paragliding Terrorist Leaves Family in Israel Fearing His Fate</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/paragliding-terrorist-leaves-family-in-israel-fearing-his-fate-1247813</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Israel</str>
    <str name="longitude">34.851612</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.046051</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Hideout Busted in Jammu and Kashmir's Poonch</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/jammu-news/terrorist-hideout-busted-in-jammu-and-kashmir-1247316</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">SRK equated with terrorist for flagging off intolerance</str>
    <str name="body">Superstar Shah Rukh Khan, speaking on his 50th birthday earlier this month, had added his voice to the growing chorus of "intolerance", drawing vicious comments from BJP leaders as well as fringe elements. "I do think there is intolerance... extreme intolerance... People just put words in the air even before thinking and here is a secular country," he had said. BJP leader Kailash Vijayvargiya said Khan's "heart lay in Pakistan". Even as the party, then battling the Bihar polls, tried to distance itself, party MP Yogi Adityanath lashed out, saying Khan should heed 26/11 attack mastermind Hafiz Saeed's advice since "they speak the same language". Saeed had tweeted all "persecuted" Muslims were welcome in Pakistan. Security had to be ramped up at his bungalow and the issue went on the backburner after the BJP was trounced in the Bihar polls.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/mumbai/SRK-equated-with-terrorist-for-flagging-off-intolerance/articleshow/49913568.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Issues Global Travel Alert Due to 'Increased Terrorist Threats'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-issues-global-travel-alert-due-to-increased-terrorist-threats-1246800</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Moroccan Woman Mistaken For Paris Terrorist, Says Pics Sold by Friend</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/moroccan-woman-mistaken-for-paris-terrorist-says-pics-sold-by-friend-1246911</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-23T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Killed in Gunbattle in North Kashmir's Kupwara District</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-killed-in-gunbattle-in-north-kashmirs-kupwara-district-1246488</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Gunbattle</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-23T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'Operations under way' in Belgium linked to 'terrorist threat': Police</str>
    <str name="body">BRUSSELS: Belgian police have launched several operations linked to the terrorist threat facing Brussels, which is under a top security alert over fears of Paris-style attacks, a spokesman said on Sunday. Different operations are under way because of the terrorist threat, a police spokesman told AFP, requesting that the media do not comment directly on the actions under way, mentioning the places for example. The public prosecutor will hold a news conference when it is all over, he added.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/europe/Operations-under-way-in-Belgium-linked-to-terrorist-threat-Police/articleshow/49886525.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Belgium</str>
    <str name="longitude">4.64150238</str>
    <str name="lattitude">50.64896393</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">It’s a journey from being angry to being a potential terrorist: Adam Deen</str>
    <str name="body">Adam Deen, a former Islamist in his 30s, lives in London. As a teenager, he joined the Al-Muhajiroun, a radical Islamist group which is linked to many terror attacks in the UK, including the 7/7 London bombings. It's been 10 years since Adam severed links with al-Muhajiroun. Now, a senior researcher at Quilliam Foundation, a London-based think tank, he works to put out a counter-narrative to radical Islamists. Deen tells Rakhi Chakrabarty over phone from London about his journey into and out of the world of Islamists. How did you get introduced to a dangerous group like the Al-Muhajiroun? I came across it while studying information technology at the University of Westminster. This is the same university where Jihadi John (an Islamic State militant) studied. He may have joined it after I left. As an immigrant in the UK, did you face problems growing up that pushed you towards a radical cult? I was born in London. My parents came to London from Turkey for work in 1970s. Ours was a secular liberal family, where Islam was a culture not an ideology. My mother wore Western clothes. I wasn't interested in religion or politics. I never had a problem. I was not angry or disenfranchised. At university, I started talking to extremist organizations and engaging with them. I was in my teens. I wanted to learn about my faith. They presented an intellectual version of Islam, something I had not heard before. They made Islam seem relevant. As a young Western Muslim, I was captivated. My lifestyle changed. I stopped socializing with my old friends, family and people of the opposite sex as I believed they were misguided and not good Muslims. I looked down upon my parents and thought they were inadequate Muslims. I had found a different circle of friends. I was living and breathing what the Islamists told me. I was very proud of the organization. Up until then, Islam was something distant. When I went to their lectures, they would talk about the Prophet and religious identity. From a British Muslim, I became a Muslim in Britain. I felt closer to the Muslim world and shunned British values. I was politicized and anti-American. I wasn't looking for adventure. I genuinely felt the need to be a better Muslim. My parents were oblivious to my transformation. About a year after joining the organization, they saw me on TV presenting Islamist views. One day, my dad found me giving out leaflets about the establishment of the Islamic Caliphate at a mosque. He was embarrassed. He told me I was hanging around with bad people. I ignored him. Is it only the urge to be a better Muslim that draws youth to radicals? Adverse economic and social conditions that disenfranchise young Muslims are contributing factors. They feel they don't have a voice. They are open to listening to anti-establishment attacks to carrying out more violent acts. It's a journey from being angry to being a potential terrorist. Islamists present a binary view where the world is split up into good and evil. All that is good is on the side of Islam. The West and everyone else is evil. They make committing crime and violence seem acceptable. They dehumanize. They promote victimhood of Muslims. When did you start getting disillusioned? At a much later stage, somebody older to me left the organization. He talked to me. There were also questions in my mind about what I was doing. I also took to studying Western philosophy with a mentor. My critical faculties were developed. I could see that there was more knowledge outside the (extremist) organization. What I was being told seemed untenable. It was a slow process of dissent. The extremist version of Islam seemed a deviation from what Islam really is. Over time, I drifted away. When they found out, I was faced with much hostility. Islamists are hostile to criticism. You can't ask questions. I was called an apostate and a betrayer and told that I should be executed. But, it was too late for them. What is the counter-narrative you are working on? The counter-narrative to Islamists is a challenge. We are trying to debunk their world view and counter their theological discourse. Those who interpret Islam as anti-rationalistic and at odds with basic ethical principles have a disproportionate hold on Muslims. While proclaiming Islam as a rational religion, they argue that killing apostates is Islamic. I believe in Islam that's tolerant, liberal and encourages freedom. It's important for Muslims to be self-critical. After leaving Islamists, I was free to explore Islam and its rich intellectual heritage. But when you speak out against status quo, there's a backlash. My aim is very clear. We have to identify, isolate and challenge their toxic theologic view, call it out within our communities.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//home/sunday-times/all-that-matters/Its-a-journey-from-being-angry-to-being-a-potential-terrorist-Adam-Deen/articleshow/49874232.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Japan's terrorist monitoring unit to maintain four bases abroad: in Jordan, Egypt, Indonesia and India</str>
    <str name="body">In the wake of the Paris attacks, the government speeds up plans for the Foreign Ministry’s new intelligence-gathering unit to begin terrorist monitoring operations overseas.</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2015/11/21/national/japans-planned-terrorist-monitoring-unit-will-four-bases-abroad-jordan-egypt-indonesia-india/</str>
    <str name="source">japantimes</str>
    <str name="location">Japan</str>
    <str name="longitude">139.0772705</str>
    <str name="lattitude">36.28164673</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Indian-American Woman Killed in Mali Terrorist Attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/indians-abroad/indian-american-woman-killed-in-mali-terrorist-attack-1245871</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Mali</str>
    <str name="longitude">-3.996166</str>
    <str name="lattitude">17.570692</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Indian-American killed in Mali terrorist attack</str>
    <str name="body">WASHINGTON : An Indian-American is among at least 27 people killed during a deadly siege of a Mali hotel by Islamic extremists. Anita Ashok Datar, 41, is the sole US citizen to have been killed in the attack on Friday, state department spokesman John Kirby said. We mourn American Anita Datar and all those lost in Mali Attacks, US secretary of state John Kerry said in a tweet on Friday. We extend condolences to family and friends and stand with the Malian people, he said. In a statement released through the US State Department, Datar's her family said that they are devastated by the news. READ ALSO: Gunmen kill 27 at Mali hotel, all Indians freed We are devastated that Anita is gone--it's unbelievable to us that she has been killed in this senseless act of violence and terrorism, the family said. Anita lived in Takoma Park in Maryland, a suburb of Washington DC. Anita was one of the kindest and most generous people we know. She loved her family and her work tremendously, the statement said. Everything she did in her life she did to help others-- as a mother, public health expert, daughter, sister and friend, it said. Datar was born in western Massachusetts and grew up in northern New Jersey. She earned an MPH and MPA from Columbia University's Joseph Mailman School of Public Health and School of International and Public Affairs. She worked in Senegal for two years with the Peace Corps (1997-1999) and spent much of her career working to advance global health and international development, with a focus on population and reproductive health, family planning and HIV. She was a senior manager at Palladium Group and a founding member of Tulalens, a not-for-profit organisation connecting underserved communities with quality health services. Armed extremists stormed Radisson Blu hotel in Mali's capital town locking in 170 people, killing at least 27 of them. Twenty captured Indians were evacuated without any harm. Complete coverage: Islamist gunmen attack luxury hotel in Mali capital</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/Indian-American-killed-in-Mali-terrorist-attack/articleshow/49868756.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Mali</str>
    <str name="longitude">-3.996166</str>
    <str name="lattitude">17.570692</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">France to Keep Border Checks as Long as 'Terrorist Threat' Lasts</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/france-to-keep-border-checks-as-long-as-terrorist-threat-lasts-1245693</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">France</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.33826232</str>
    <str name="lattitude">46.63727951</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">28 'Terrorist Group Members' Shot Dead in China's Xinjiang: Authorities</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/28-terrorist-group-members-shot-dead-in-chinas-xinjiang-authorities-1245480</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">China Xinjiang</str>
    <str name="longitude">111.0703888</str>
    <str name="lattitude">35.70793533</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">28 'terrorist group members' shot dead in China's Xinjiang</str>
    <str name="body">BEIJING: Chinese security forces in the far western region of Xinjiang killed 28 terrorists from a group that carried out a deadly attack at a coal mine in September under the direction of foreign extremists, the regional government said on Friday. The news carried by the government-run Xinjiang Daily was the first official mention of the September 18 attack at the Sogan colliery in Aksu, in which it said 16 people, including 5 police officers were killed, and another 18 people injured. Radio Free Asia, which first reported the incident about two months ago, said at least 50 people had died. Attackers fled into the mountains and authorities launched a manhunt with more than 10,000 people participating every day, forming an inescapable dragnet, the Xinjiang Daily said. After 56 days of continuous fighting, Xinjiang destroyed a violent terrorist gang directly under the command of a foreign extremist group. Aside from one person who surrendered, 28 thugs were completely annihilated, the newspaper said. China's government says it faces a serious threat from Islamist militants and separatists in energy-rich Xinjiang, on the border of central Asia, where hundreds have died in violence in recent years. Rights groups say China has never presented convincing evidence of the existence of a cohesive militant group fighting the government. Much of the unrest, they argue, is due to frustration at controls over the culture and religion of the Uighur people who live in Xinjiang, a charge Beijing denies. The Xinjiang Daily said two people who appeared to have Uighur names were leaders of the unnamed foreign group. Beginning in 2008, the Xinjiang group's members began watching extremist videos and communicated six times with an extremist group outside of China's borders, requesting tactical guidance, the paper said. Members of this foreign extremist group transmitted orders to the gang many times and demanded pledges of loyalty, it said, without elaborating. It is unclear why the government had not disclosed the incident earlier. Officials says some Uighurs have gone to fight with radical groups in the Middle East. Western nations have been reluctant to cooperate in China's anti-terrorism campaign in Xinjiang, nervous about being implicated in possible human rights abuses, accusations China denies. Since last week's attacks in Paris, Chinese state media has lambasted Western countries for their double standards on terrorism.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/china/28-terrorist-group-members-shot-dead-in-Chinas-Xinjiang/articleshow/49854534.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">China Xinjiang</str>
    <str name="longitude">111.0703888</str>
    <str name="lattitude">35.70793533</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Suspect Sought in Sweden for 'Planning Terrorist Act': Police</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/suspect-sought-in-sweden-for-planning-terrorist-act-police-1244945</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Sweden</str>
    <str name="longitude">18.643501</str>
    <str name="lattitude">60.12816100000001</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Canadian Sikh Wrongly Pictured as Paris Terrorist; Image Photoshopped</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/indians-abroad/canadian-sikh-wrongly-pictured-as-paris-terrorist-image-photoshopped-1244151</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Spanish daily wrongly labels Canadian Sikh as 'terrorist'</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: On Sunday, Veerender Jubbal woke up and found himself infamous. He was front page news in Spain, with newspaper La Razon claiming he was one of the terrorists involved in the Paris massacre this Saturday. The Sikh writer and journalist from Canada found an innocuous bathroom selfie had been photoshopped with a Quran in his hand and a suicide vest over his torso. The image had been splashed over European media and the Internet. The online community soon came forward to dispel the falsehood, sharing the original picture, where a smiling Jubbal is clicking a picture of himself with an iPad (later photoshopped into a copy of the Quran), camera facing a mirror. Besides La Razon and an Italian news channel called Sky committed the same error. Veerender Jubbal was among the national trends in Spain on Sunday. La Razon tweeted an apology later from their official account in Spanish saying: Yesterday we erroneously published a picture of @Veeren_Jubbal confusing him with one of the Paris terrorists. We ask for your pardon. At the time of writing, the origin of the photoshopped image had not yet been traced. Both Jubbal, who has over 11,000 Twitter followers, and his friends and supporters carried out an intense round of firefighting through Sunday and most of Monday, tweeting the original pictures and setting the record straight. After explaining what had transpired, and soliciting messages of support, Jubbal tweeted: You can all check the last retweets. Let us start with basics. Never been to Paris. Am a Sikh dude with a turban. Lives in Canada. He also tweeted about getting a phone call from a cousin in India, who saw the coverage. Jubbal said he might sue the media agencies responsible. Jubbal could not be contacted at the time of going to press. Had this been under the Indian law, says lawyer Apar Gupta, the law of torts would apply. A person can take refuge under the tort of emotional distress, and claim monetary compensation for the anticipated harm and the distress caused, says Gupta. The harm in this case, could have been chillingly real. Rohini Lakshane, a researcher with the Bengaluru-based Center for Internet and Society prescribes using technical means to tell hoax from truth. There are technical means for figuring out if an image has been doctored, there are websites such as Snopes and Hoax Slayer that debunk falsified stories, there is keen observation needed to spot the holes in a hoax or a rumour, and there is common sense. As for the media outlets that published the doctored image, it was irresponsible of them to pass on an unverified piece of news. Sometimes content published on satire websites and 'fictitious news' websites finds its way into newspapers and broadcast as legitimate news. The only way to counter the spread of online hoaxes is to fight misinformation with information. Jubbal is no stranger to online harassment. Since 2014, he had been at the receiving end of vicious abuse for speaking out against non-diverse and unequal depictions of races and genders in online gaming. While some friends and supporters of Jubbal conveyed deep disgust at the recent virtual attack, often devolving into profanities, the man himself remained calm and graceful through it all. The most strongly worded tweet from him read: Learn the difference between me being a Sikh, and a Muslim. Cry in mug, while I use your tears to water my garden. I am valuable, and rad.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/rest-of-world/Spanish-daily-wrongly-labels-Canadian-Sikh-as-terrorist/articleshow/49810629.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attacks cast Paris into ‘an impossible nightmare’</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.taipeitimes.comNews/editorials/archives/2015/11/16/2003632560</str>
    <str name="source">edit-taiwan</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Russia Says Hezbollah Not a Terrorist Group: Report</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russia-says-hezbollah-not-a-terrorist-group-report-1243882</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Russia</str>
    <str name="longitude">105.318756</str>
    <str name="lattitude">61.52401</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Govt declares NSCN (K) as terrorist organization</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: The National Socialist Council of Nagaland-Khaplang (NSCN-K), all its formations and front organisations were declared as terrorist organisations on Monday by the ministry of home affairs. The government has declared the NSCN-K, all its formations and front organisations as a terrorist organization under the Unlawful Activities (Prevention) Act, 1967, said a statement issued here. NSCN-K, a militant outfit, came into existence in 1988 and is active along the India-Myanmar border, according to a gazette notification issued on November 6. NSCN-K has resorted to terrorism by killing innocent civilians and security forces and engaged in other violent activities, including the June 4, 2015, attack on the army convoy in Chandel district of Manipur, it added.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Govt-declares-NSCN-K-as-terrorist-organization/articleshow/49799142.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Algerian investment chief calls on Japanese firms to return after crackdown on terrorist groups</str>
    <str name="body">The head of the Algerian government agency that promotes inbound investment has called on Japanese firms to return, saying strict safety measures have been enacted since the hostage crisis at the Ain Amenas gas plant in January 2013 that left 10 Japanese dead. “We ...</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2015/11/15/national/algerian-investment-chief-calls-japanese-firms-return-crackdown-terrorist-groups/</str>
    <str name="source">japantimes</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Suspected ISIS Terrorist Blows Himself Up in Turkey, G20 Summit Host: Reports</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/suspected-isis-terrorist-blows-himself-up-in-turkey-4-cops-injured-reports-1243573</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Turkey</str>
    <str name="longitude">34.93033981</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.05101013</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'Profoundly Shocked' by Paris 'Terrorist' Attacks: Angela Merkel</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/profoundly-shocked-by-paris-terrorist-attacks-angela-merkel-1243228</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UN Chief Condemns 'Despicable Terrorist Attacks' in Paris</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/un-chief-condemns-despicable-terrorist-attacks-in-paris-1243230</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Paris</str>
    <str name="longitude">2.352222</str>
    <str name="lattitude">48.856614</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pakistan Strongly Condemns Terrorist Attacks in Paris</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/pakistan-strongly-condemns-terrorist-attacks-in-paris-1243400</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Top NDFB(S) Terrorist Killed in Encounter in Assam</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/top-ndfb-s-terrorist-killed-in-encounter-in-assam-1243475</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Assam</str>
    <str name="longitude">92.937574</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.200604</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Air Strike Targets Islamic State Terrorist 'Jihadi John' in Syria: Pentagon</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/islamic-state-terrorist-jihadi-john-targeted-in-us-air-strike-reports-1242897</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">White House condemns 'horrific terrorist attacks' in Beirut</str>
    <str name="body">WASHINGTON: The White House condemned the horrific terrorist twin bomb blasts claimed by the Islamic State extremist group that killed 41 people in Beirut on Thursday. Such acts of terror only reinforce our commitment to support the institutions of the Lebanese state, including the security services, to ensure a stable, sovereign, and secure Lebanon, national security council spokesman Ned Price said in a statement.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/White-House-condemns-horrific-terrorist-attacks-in-Beirut/articleshow/49763397.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Beirut</str>
    <str name="longitude">35.50677872</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.89606857</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US airstrike targets Islamic State terrorist 'Jihadi John'</str>
    <str name="body">WASHINGTON: The Pentagon says US forces have conducted an airstrike in Syria targeting the British man known as Jihadi John who participated in the beheading videos of two American journalists and the slayings of several other captives. Pentagon press secretary Peter Cook says the airstrike on Thursday in Raqqa targeted Mohamed Emwazi. Cook says whether or not Emwazi died in the strike is not clear. A US official says a drone had targeted a vehicle believed to be carrying Emwazi. The official is not authorized to speak publicly and requested anonymity. Emwazi is in the videos showing the killings of journalists Steven Sotloff and James Foley, US aid worker Abdul-Rahman Kassig, British aid workers David Haines and Alan Henning, Japanese journalist Kenji Goto, and a number of other hostages. Read this story in Telugu: జిహాదీ జాన్‌ను చంపడమే లక్ష్యం</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/US-airstrike-targets-Islamic-State-terrorist-Jihadi-John/articleshow/49764427.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">IS terrorist Jihadi John 'killed by drone strike'</str>
    <str name="body">American defence officials have said they are almost certain they have killed the British militant known as Jihadi John in a drone strike. Mohammed Emwazi, who appeared in a series of gory propaganda videos showing the beheading of foreign journalists and aid workers last year, was targeted in the ISIS stronghold of Raqqa last night. There has been no official confirmation of his death but a senior US military official told Fox News: We are 99 per cent sure we got him. Another official speaking to ABC News described the air strike that as a flawless and clean hit that evaporated Emwazi without killing civilians. Activists from anti-ISIS group Raqqa is Being Slaughtered Silently said a drone targeted the car Emwazi was travelling in near the Islamic Court, which enforces the group's interpretation of Sharia law, in the city centre. A Facebook post said the first explosion hit at around 11.41pm local time (9.41pm GMT) and that around a dozen more air strikes were counted before midnight. A senior US military source told the BBC Emwazi had been tracked carefully over a period of time and that there is a high degree of certainty that the mission was a success. At least one other person is believed to have in the car when it was hit. The Pentagon has confirmed the air strike but said it would not formally announce the result until it had been fully assessed. A spokesperson for Downing Street said: We are aware of the US statement about the airstrike targeting Mohammed Emwazi. Like them, we are not commenting further at this stage. Emwazi, who was born in Kuwait but moved to London as a child, is believed to have travelled to Syria in 2013 to join the so-called Islamic State. He gained his nickname from his part in a group of British militants dubbed The Beatles by fellow jihadists. The former IT student rose to prominence after appearing in a video showing the murder of US journalist James Foley in August last year. Emwazi then appeared in videos showing the deaths of American journalist Steven Sotloff, British aid worker David Haines and UK taxi driver Alan Henning, US aid worker Abdul-Rahman Kassig and Japanese journalist Kenji Goto. Wearing a black robe and balaclava, he claimed the attacks were revenge for British and American foreign policy and was not identified until February this year.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//articleshow/49768103.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Sikh radicals 'appoint' convicted terrorist as Akal Takht chief</str>
    <str name="body">AMRITSAR: Deepening the crisis within Sikh religious affairs, radical Sikhs on Tuesday announced the appointment of convicted Khalistani terrorist Jagtar Singh Hawara as the Jathedar (chief) of the Akal Takht, the highest temporal seat of the Sikh religion. The congregation of radicals also announced the removal of all Sikh high priests. The appointment was announced by radical Sikh leaders during a 'Sarbat Khalsa' (grand assembly of Sikhs) congregation at Chaba near Amritsar on Tuesday. Hawara is the main accused in the assassination of then Punjab chief minister Beant Singh who was killed by a human bomb in Chandigarh on August 31, 1995. The congregation decided that the present Akal Takht Jathedar Gurbachan Singh be removed from his post and that Hawara, who is serving a life term in the Beant Singh assassination case, be appointed. During the congregation, in view of Hawara being in prison, the leaders announced that former MP D.S. Mand would be the interim jathedar of the Akal Takht and would address the Sikh community from the shrine, located inside the Golden Temple complex, on Diwali on Wednesday. The congregation was organised by a few radical Sikh groups. Accusing them of genocide of Sikhs, the congregation named former police chief K.P.S. Gill and Operation Bluestar commander K.S. Brar, both Sikhs themselves, as 'tankhaiya' (person guilty of religious misconduct) and directed them to appear before the Akal Takht by November 20.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/amritsar/Sikh-radicals-appoint-convicted-terrorist-as-Akal-Takht-chief/articleshow/49746076.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-03T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Fewer civilians killed, but terrorist violence up in JandK</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: Terrorist violence in Jammu and Kashmir this year has surpassed the levels recorded in 2014, with 169 incidents and 35 security personnel killed until October 25 as compared to 167 incidents and 30 force casualties in the corresponding period last year. Though 86 terrorists were neutralized till October 25 against 83 in the same period of 2014 and the civilian casualties caused while maintaining law and order stagnated at four, the number of civilian killings by the militants fell to 16 from 20 last year. READ ALSO: Two militants killed in encounter in Jammu and Kashmir The latest statistics mark a year-on-year increase in most terror indices related to JandK. In fact, at 169 incidents until October 25, the figure of 170 incidents recorded in the whole of 2014 is set to be surpassed soon. Nevertheless, incidents have shown a steady decline from the high of 488 recorded in 2010, followed by 340 in 2011 and 220 in 2012. The security forces killed in terrorism-related incidents is lower than 2013 but higher than the 2011 and 2012 figure. Terrorists, wary of losing ground support, are going after security forces more than civilians. Civilian killings have fallen from 28 in 2014, though they exceeded the levels (15 fatal casualties) seen in 2012 and 2013. The security forces are not taking the higher casualties lying down and are retaliating in equal measure to terrorist attacks. As many as 86 terrorists were killed until October 25, as compared to 67 in 2013 and 72 in 2012. It remains to be seen if the 2015 figure of terrorist killings will surpass the 2014 mark of 110. According to home ministry sources, around 200-220 terrorists/militants, both local and foreign, are estimated to be holed up in the Valley. Though they possess arms, not many are actively engaging security forces in encounters. This could be due to their poor and inadequate training. Earlier, militants could exfiltrate and train at camps in PoK but the heightened vigil by Indian forces at the border has made this a difficult proposition... not many local recruits are well-versed in the use of arms, which has made them less of a worry to the security agencies, a senior officer in the security establishment told TOI. Sources said much of the local recruitment was taking place in Tral and Pulwama. Many of the new recruits are unable to adapt to the hard life of a militant that involves living in the jungles... they are not as committed or hardened and there have been some cases of these terrorists wanting to return to their families, the officer said.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Fewer-civilians-killed-but-terrorist-violence-up-in-JK/articleshow/49637624.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-11-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'For Terrorist Like Osama, Sonia Gandhi Would Cry All Night': Minister Mukhtar Abbas Naqvi</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/for-terrorist-like-osama-sonia-gandhi-would-cry-all-night-minister-mukhtar-abbas-naqvi-1238923</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Mother of Islamic State Terrorist Jailed for Supporting Son's Activities on Facebook</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/mother-of-islamic-state-terrorist-jailed-for-supporting-sons-activities-on-facebook-1236035</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Killed in Gun Battle in Jammu and Kashmir's Baramulla</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-killed-in-gunbattle-in-jammu-and-kashmirs-baramulla-1234778</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Russia's Vladimir Putin Says Terrorist Groups Seek to Destabilise More Regions After Syria: Report</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russias-vladimir-putin-says-terrorist-groups-seek-to-destabilise-more-regions-after-syria-report-1234497</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Russia</str>
    <str name="longitude">105.318756</str>
    <str name="lattitude">61.52401</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">2 Injured After Burqa-Clad Terrorist Opens Fire in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/2-injured-after-terrorist-opens-fire-in-south-kashmirs-pulwama-district-1232935</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Soldier, terrorist killed as army foils infiltration in JandK</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/jammu/Soldier-terrorist-killed-as-army-foils-infiltration-in-JK/articleshow/49376105.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Soldier, Terrorist Killed as Army Foils Infiltration in Jammu and Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/soldier-terrorist-killed-as-army-foils-infiltration-in-jammu-and-kashmir-1232260</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">70-Year-Old Sikh Terrorist Waryam Singh to be Freed, Decides Home Ministry</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/70-year-old-sikh-terrorist-waryam-singh-to-be-freed-decides-home-ministry-1231456</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Sangeet Som alleges university under Azam Khan's patronage indulging in terrorist activities</str>
    <str name="body">UNKNOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/lucknow/Sangeet-Som-alleges-university-under-Azam-Khans-patronage-indulging-in-terrorist-activities/articleshow/49334849.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Sangeet Som alleges university under Azam Khan's patronage indulging in terrorist activities</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/lucknow/Sangeet-Som-alleges-university-under-Azam-Khans-patronage-indulging-in-terrorist-activities/articleshow/49334849.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Ankara bombing: Investigation into Turkey's deadliest terrorist attack to be 'completely focused' on Isis</str>
    <str name="body">UNKNOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/europe/Ankara-bombing-Investigation-into-Turkeys-deadliest-terrorist-attack-to-be-completely-focused-on-Isis/articleshow/49319593.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Ankara</str>
    <str name="longitude">32.86050034</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.94290161</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Ankara bombing: Investigation into Turkey's deadliest terrorist attack to be 'completely focused' on Isis</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/europe/Ankara-bombing-Investigation-into-Turkeys-deadliest-terrorist-attack-to-be-completely-focused-on-Isis/articleshow/49319593.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Ankara</str>
    <str name="longitude">32.86050034</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.94290161</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Spencer Stone, Airman Who Foiled Terrorist Attack, Is Stabbed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/spencer-stone-airman-who-foiled-terrorist-attack-is-stabbed-1230011</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Abhijeet Bhattacharya: Ghulam Ali a 'dengue artist' from 'terrorist country'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//entertainment/hindi/music/news/Abhijeet-Bhattacharya-Ghulam-Ali-a-dengue-artist-from-terrorist-country/articleshow/49283190.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Police Officer Killed in Terrorist Attack in North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/police-officer-killed-in-terrorist-attack-in-north-kashmir-1229355</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Attacks Hit GDP, Hurt Investments: Moody's</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://profit.ndtv.com/news/economy/article-terrorist-attacks-hit-gdp-hurt-investments-moodys-1228603</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">1 Terrorist Killed In An Encounter In Jammu And Kashmir's Kupwara</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/1-terrorist-killed-in-an-encounter-in-jammu-and-kashmirs-kupwara-1226147</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-10-04T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Bangladeshi Terrorist Arrested in Burdwan Blast Case Had Aadhaar, Election Card</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/bangladeshi-terrorist-arrested-in-burdwan-blast-case-had-aadhaar-election-card-1226092</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Attack During Cricket Match in Afghanistan, Nine Dead And Above 50 Wounded</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://sports.ndtv.com/article/249218</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Afghanistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">67.709953</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.93911</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist China misleads rival US</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.taipeitimes.comNews/editorials/archives/2015/09/26/2003628601</str>
    <str name="source">edit-taiwan</str>
    <str name="location">China</str>
    <str name="longitude">120.6545022</str>
    <str name="lattitude">24.2225023</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Most Wanted Terrorist Among 7 Arrested by Security Forces in Assam</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/most-wanted-terrorist-among-7-arrested-by-security-forces-in-assam-1222976</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Assam</str>
    <str name="longitude">92.937574</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.200604</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Review: Quantico Flips Between Jousting FBI Recruits and a Terrorist Attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://movies.ndtv.com/television/review-quantico-flips-between-jousting-fbi-recruits-and-a-terrorist-attack-1222904</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">LeT terrorist held in Kashmir: Army</str>
    <str name="body">SRINAGAR: The army said it apprehended a Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) terrorist in Jammu and Kashmir's Kupwara district on Wednesday. "Army today (Wednesday) morning apprehended one LeT terrorist from Drushpura forests, Handwara in Kupwara district," said defence spokesman, Lt Col NN Joshi. He said a surveillance team of Rashtriya Rifles unit operating in the area found a man moving "under suspicious circumstances" and recovered a 9 mm pistol for him. "On further investigation he revealed his identity to be Bilal Ahmed Nazar, resident of Chhan Mohalla, Badrahar (Kupwara) and led the team to recovery of an AK-47 rifle and other war-like stores," said Joshi, adding that the arrested man has been handed over to police in Handwara for further investigations.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/srinagar/LeT-terrorist-held-in-Kashmir-Army/articleshow/49084582.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">LeT terrorist held in Kashmir: Army</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/srinagar/LeT-terrorist-held-in-Kashmir-Army/articleshow/49084582.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Killed in Gunfight at Pulwama in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-killed-in-gunfight-at-pulwama-in-kashmir-1220463</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pulwama</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.014382</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.981889</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Rights of a terrorist cannot hold primacy, says Rajnath Singh</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Rights-of-a-terrorist-cannot-hold-primacy-says-Rajnath-Singh/articleshow/49029882.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Rights of a terrorist cannot hold primacy, says Rajnath Singh</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: Nearly one and half months after Yakub Memon was hanged for his role in 1993 serial blasts in Mumbai, home minister Rajnath Singh took a jibe at those opposing his execution as he lamented that some human rights activists raise their voices in favour of terrorists. Speaking at a meeting of National Human Rights Commission and its state units on Friday, Singh said Yakub was hanged after completion of the judicial process. "He was convicted by the highest court of the country - the Supreme Court. But in that case also, some people tried to raise the issue of human rights ... I fail to understand why such things are raised," he said. "Some people tend to give importance to the rights of a terrorist over the rights of security forces," the minister said adding that India has a healthy democracy but no one could hold the nation to ransom with guns in hands. READ ALSO: ​'Yakub Memon does not deserve to be hanged' Games played in Yakub Memon's case Memon was hanged on July 30. Even after his mercy plea was rejected twice, some activists approached the Chief Justice of India well past midnight, hours before the hanging seeking postponement of the execution in an unprecedented development. The apex court held the final hearing past 2am on July 30. Singh said human rights have been an integral part of Indian culture and Indian saints have highlighted the idea of rights of whole universe, including plants and animals. Singh also expressed concern over prisoners languishing in jails for years before the case is decided. "It is a serious matter and we all have to address it. We have already written to the state governments to take necessary action," he said. Expressing concern over human trafficking, he called for detailed Standard Operating Procedures SOPs) for re-integration, repatriation and rehabilitation of the victims.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Rights-of-a-terrorist-cannot-hold-primacy-says-Rajnath-Singh/articleshow/49029882.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Bullet-Riddled Body of Hizbul Mujahideen Terrorist Found in North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/bullet-riddled-body-of-hizbul-mujahideen-terrorist-found-in-north-kashmir-1219358</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">3-Year-Old Shot Dead Along With Father, a Former Terrorist, in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/3-year-old-shot-dead-along-with-father-a-former-terrorist-in-kashmir-1219455</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Former Terrorist, 3-Year-Old Son Shot Dead At Their Home in Sopore</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/former-terrorist-3-year-old-son-shot-dead-at-their-home-in-sopore-1219334</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Sopore</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.4624013</str>
    <str name="lattitude">34.2867629</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Most-Wanted Lashkar Terrorist, Carrying Reward of Rs 10 Lakh, Killed in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/most-wanted-lashkar-terrorist-carrying-reward-of-rs-10-lakh-killed-in-kashmir-1216959</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Embassy in South Africa Issues 'Terrorist Threat' Warning</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-embassy-in-south-africa-issues-terrorist-threat-warning-1215509</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US Embassy</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Alleged Terrorist Captured Following Udhampur Attack Brought to Delhi for Lie Detector Test</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/alleged-terrorist-captured-following-udhampur-attack-brought-to-delhi-for-lie-detector-test-1214825</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Delhi</str>
    <str name="longitude">77.209021</str>
    <str name="lattitude">28.613939</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Killed in North Kashmir's Rafiabad After 9-Hour Encounter</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-killed-in-north-kashmirs-rafiabad-after-9-hour-encounter-1213552</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">North Kashmir Rafiabad</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naved Performed Security Duty at JuD Congregation: Dossier</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pak-terrorist-naved-performed-security-duty-at-jud-congregation-dossier-1213647</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Soldier Killed in Gun Battle With Terrorist in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/gun-battle-on-between-security-forces-and-terrorist-in-north-kashmir-1213434</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-09-01T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Threat from terrorist groups emanates from Pakistan: US</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/Threat-from-terrorist-groups-emanates-from-Pakistan-US/articleshow/48753400.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan US</str>
    <str name="longitude">67.05000305</str>
    <str name="lattitude">24.87000084</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-29T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Declare Pak a terrorist state: Dy CM</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/jammu/Declare-Pak-a-terrorist-state-Dy-CM/articleshow/48718959.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Second Pak Terrorist Captured was Assigned to Set Up Lashkar Network</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/second-pak-terrorist-captured-was-assigned-to-set-up-lashkar-launchpad-1212072</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Lashkar Network</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Captured Today is 22, Says His Name is Javed Ahmed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pak-terrorist-captured-today-is-22-says-his-name-is-javed-ahmed-1211680</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Second Pakistani Terrorist Caught After Encounter in North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pakistani-terrorist-caught-alive-after-encounter-in-north-kashmir-1211556</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">North Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Tear Gas, 'Chilli Grenades' Used to Force Pak Terrorist Out of Cave</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/cheat-sheet/chilly-grenades-used-by-army-to-flush-pakistani-terrorist-out-of-cave-reports-1211698</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Naveed Makes Confessional Statement in Court in Jammu</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-naveed-makes-confessional-statement-in-court-in-jammu-1211281</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Killed in Encounter in Kashmir's Uri Sector</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-killed-in-encounter-in-kashmirs-uri-sector-1211154</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Designates Abdul Aziz Haqqani as 'Global Terrorist'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-designates-abdul-aziz-haqqani-as-global-terrorist-1211139</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">HuJI terrorist Shaik Noor produced before court</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/hyderabad/HuJI-terrorist-Shaik-Noor-produced-before-court/articleshow/48675768.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Naved's statement to be recorded today</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-Naveds-statement-to-be-recorded-today/articleshow/48677723.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">LeT terrorist Naved to make statement in court on Wednesday</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/LeT-terrorist-Naved-to-make-statement-in-court-on-Wednesday/articleshow/48660827.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Captured Pakistani terrorist sent to judicial custody</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/jammu/Captured-Pakistani-terrorist-sent-to-judicial-custody/articleshow/48664368.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak terrorist Naved before CJM for recording statement</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/jammu/Pak-terrorist-Naved-before-CJM-for-recording-statement/articleshow/48664381.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Captured Pakistani terrorist sent to judicial custody</str>
    <str name="body">Jammu: A court here on Monday sent Udhampur terror attack accused Muhammad Naveed alias Qasim Khan, a Pakistani national, to judicial custody till August 26. Jammu's chief judicial magistrate Sunnet Gupta issued the order. The accused had earlier been on police remand for 15 days. The National Investigation Agency (NIA) is probing the Udhampur terror attack in which three people, including two BSF troopers, were killed and 11 troopers injured on the Jammu-Srinagar National highway on August 5. After escaping from the attack site, the accused had entered Chirdi village near Samroli on the highway and taken three people hostage. He was finally over-powered by his hostages and handed over to police. So far, the NIA has rounded up around half a dozen people for questioning based on identification by Naveed.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/jammu/Captured-Pakistani-terrorist-sent-to-judicial-custody/articleshow/48664368.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naveed to Record Statement Before Magistrate</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pak-terrorist-naveed-to-record-statement-before-magistrate-1210363</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Father of French Train Gunman Says Cannot Believe Son is a Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/father-of-french-train-gunman-says-cannot-believe-son-is-a-terrorist-1210458</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-23T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">‘Terrorist sleeper cells active in state’</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Terrorist-sleeper-cells-active-in-state/articleshow/48628438.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'If Pak Shows Dossier, We Will Show Them Captured Terrorist,' Says Sushma Swaraj</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/cheat-sheet/cloud-over-india-pakistan-talks-as-both-sides-reject-preconditions-1209827</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Intel agencies, police grill suspected terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Intel-agencies-police-grill-suspected-terrorist/articleshow/48591215.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naveed Had Allegedly Planned Udhampur Attack in June</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pak-terrorist-naveed-had-allegedly-planned-udhampur-attack-in-june-1209710</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Truck Driver Who Allegedly Helped Pak Terrorist Naveed Arrested by National Investigation Agency</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/truck-driver-who-allegedly-helped-pak-terrorist-naveed-arrested-1209657</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">‘Terrorist’ nabbed on Ranchi-bound train</str>
    <str name="body">Ranchi: Police arrested a suspected terrorist from a Ranchi-bound passenger train and seized a huge cache of explosives from his possession on the outskirts of the state capital on Thursday. The explosives were being transported from Burdwan ( West Bengal) to Ranchi, railway officials said. Intezar Ali, a resident of Mujahidnagar area under Hindpiri police station in Ranchi, was arrested from the Burdwan-Hatia train at Kita railway station, 45km from Ranchi. Police found 24 gelatin sticks, six crude bombs, six detonators, 250 grams each of sulphur and urea and one kg of material suspected to be RDX. Meanwhile, speculations about Ali continued to do rounds as several police sources claimed to have found coded texts in Urdu in his possession. Sources in the Ranchi division of South Eastern Railways and the police said the search and arrest were based on inputs provided by the defence intelligence on Thursday morning. "Whether the material is RDX can be only determined after further examination. As of now, the suspect is being interrogated," police spokesperson S N Pradhan said. Till late in the evening, police had not been able to establish a link between the suspect and any terror group. "The motive behind transporting explosives is still not clear. We do not know as of now where the cache was being taken to," a police officer interrogating Ali said. Pradhan said the department was open to seeking help from the National Investigating Agency (NIA) if the need arose. Meanwhile, the Ranchi railway division tightened security on all outbound express trains. Ranchi senior divisional commercial manager Neeraj Kumar said all passenger trains coming in and out of Ranchi will also be screened extensively.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Terrorist-nabbed-on-Ranchi-bound-train/articleshow/48562879.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">‘Terrorist’ nabbed on Ranchi-bound train</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Terrorist-nabbed-on-Ranchi-bound-train/articleshow/48562879.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Judge who gave death to Pak terrorist Kasab retires today</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Judge-who-gave-death-to-Pak-terrorist-Kasab-retires-today/articleshow/48572802.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Judge who gave death to Pak terrorist Kasab retires today</str>
    <str name="body">MUMBAI: Justice M L Tahilyani, who had sentenced Pakistan terrorist Mohamed Ajmal Kasab to death for his role in 26/11 Mumbai terror attacks, retires on Friday as a Bombay high court judge after 28 years of distinguished judicial service. Justice Tahilyani is slated to take up a new assignment as the Lok Ayukta of Maharashtra on August 24. Justice Tahilyani was given a fond farewell by lawyers affiliated to the Advocates Association of Western India (AAWI) in the Bombay high court on Thursday. During his tenure as a sessions judge in Mumbai, Judge Tahilyani had tried many sensational cases, including the murder cases of music baron Gulshan Kumar and trade union leader-MP Datta Samant and also the 26/11 Mumbai terror attack case in which Kasab was executed. Tahaliyani began his career in 1987 as a metropolitan magistrate in a Bandra court. He was appointed as additional sessions judge in Mumbai sessions court in 1997. He was promoted as principal judge in the city's civil and sessions court in early 2000 prior to taking up the assignment in the HC as registrar (inspection). He was appointed as a judge in the 26/11 trial in 2009. He was also posted as a special judge to handle CBI cases. The Supreme Court, in its judgement confirming the Bombay high court order on Kasab's death sentence, praised Justice Tahilyani for exemplary handling of records. The SC observed that "in the course of hearing of appeal (of Kasab), we also came to know the trial judge M L Tahilyani. From the records of the case, he appears to be stern, no-nonsense person. But he is a true flag-bearer of the rule of law in this country. The manner in which he conducted the trial and maintained the record is exemplary." In 2010, Justice Tahilyani was promoted as a judge of the Bombay HC. Felicitating Justice Tahilyani at a function organised by AAWI, senior lawyer S R Chitnis described him as an "outspoken judge." Apart from listening to advocates' arguments, he (Tahilyani) would directly ask questions to the litigants to find out the truth, Chitnis said. In his court, many couples had opted for compromise in domestic violence cases instead of moving on with litigations. "He always kept the court atmosphere tension-free, which benefitted junior lawyers. He disposed of a large number of appeals under Prevention of Corruption Act," said another senior lawyer Ashok Mundargi. _</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Judge-who-gave-death-to-Pak-terrorist-Kasab-retires-today/articleshow/48572802.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-18T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">NIA releases sketches of 2 aides of Pakistani terrorist Naved; manhunt launched</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: National Investigation Agency has released sketches of two aides of Pakistani terrorist Mohammed Naved Yakub, who was captured alive by the locals following the attack on a BSF bus in Udhampur district of Jammu on August 5 that left its two personnel dead, Times Now reported on Tuesday. The two aides of Naved are on the run and the NIA has launched a manhunt for them. Mohammed Naved Yakub is undergoing a polygraph test today. The DNA and voice samples of Naved will also be obtained by the NIA. NIA sources said collecting the DNA samples of the militant from Faislabad in Pakistan could help in proving his nationality. Islamabad has been insisting that Naved is not a Pakistani national. READ ALSO: Naved's DNA sample to be shared with Pakistan Enough evidence to prove Naved is from Pakistan, was part of LeT: NIA chief Naved was produced before district judge Amar Nath on Monday, who after holding in camera proceedings, ordered the lie detector test to be performed at 11 am on Tuesday at the Central Forensic Science Laboratory in CGO complex. Earlier, the militant gave his written consent for the test, writing in Urdu. Before being brought from Jammu last weekend, Naved, in his 20s, was confronted with other militants from Faislabad lodged in various jails and his interrogators concluded he was not lying about where he hailed from. Sources said the militant is likely to be questioned about how many people were with him when the group infiltrated Jammu and Kashmir and people he had met and lived with during his two-month stay in the state. NIA declares award for arrest of accused persons in Udhampur Attack. pic.twitter.com/htiUk4r6GK andmdash; ANI (@ANI_news) August 18, 2015 Sources in the anti-terror agency said Naved has been giving conflicting statements about the strength of the group that infiltrated the state with him and the route taken by them, besides those with whom he came into contact in JandK. He had also given wrong information about the registration plate number of the vehicle that carried him and accomplice Noman to 'Tamatar Modh' on Jammu-Srinagar on August 4, lest it would expose those helping the terror group. Naved has told his interrogators he was often administered psychotropic substances by his Lashkar-e-Taiba handler who motivated him to wage 'Jihad' in India. He was also promised he would be rehabilitated in Pakistan with cash rewards after he carried out 5-6 terror attacks in India. The young militant also told NIA that LeT had threatened his family with dire consequences if they made a hue and cry over his joining the terror network. Naved's accomplice Mohammed Noman alias Momin was killed in retaliatory firing by the BSF. (With inputs from agencies) READ IN HINDI: NIA ने जारी किए दो फरार पाकिस्तानी एजेंसियों के स्केच</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/NIA-releases-sketches-of-2-aides-of-Pakistani-terrorist-Naved-manhunt-launched/articleshow/48524619.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-18T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">NIA releases sketches of 2 aides of Pakistani terrorist Naved; manhunt launched</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/NIA-releases-sketches-of-2-aides-of-Pakistani-terrorist-Naved-manhunt-launched/articleshow/48524619.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Naveed Identified Home in Pakistan on Google Earth: Sources</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/naved-nia-investigation-1208128</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">HuJI terrorist Jabbar roamed freely in India</str>
    <str name="body">HYDERABAD: Bangladesh-based Harkat-ul-Jihadi Al-Islami (HuJI) terrorist Abdul Jabbar freely roamed across India for a few months and then slipped into Bangladesh through the porous border in Malda (West Bengal) with ease in 2013. This startling revelation came to light during the interrogation of Pakistani national Mohammed Nasir, who allegedly has close links with Jabbar. Nasir along with Bangladeshi nationals Faizal Mohamoud, Joynal Abedin, Maynmarese national Zia Ur Rehman and two local agents — Masood Ali Khan and Parvez Khan — was arrested by the Hyderabad police in a pre-dawn swoop at their hideout at Chanchalguda on Friday. Police sources told STOI that Jabbar entered India by illegally crossing the border in Malda and stayed in the country for a few months, probably after the Dilsukhnagar blasts in 2013. However, Jabbar's activities in the country never came under the scanner of either central or state intelligence agencies. "Nasir disclosed that after Jabbar illegally entered India, they both moved together in Uttar Pradesh, West Bengal and Bihar before the HuJI terrorist slipped back into Bangladesh without any hassle. Jabbar, however, did not visit Hyderabad or other districts of Telangana. We have to probe further what they did and whom they met during Jabbar's stay in India,'' a senior officer, who is part of the investigation team, told STOI. Jabbar, who reportedly has links with Indian Mujahideen (IM) founders Riyaz Bhatkal and Yasin Bhatkal, directed Nasir in January 2014 to help the Dilsukhnagar blast accused Waqas alias Sonu to escape to Bangladesh, the source said. "Nasir met Waqas and helped him cross the Malda border in West Bengal to reach Bangladesh, unaware of the latter's antecedents. Nasir came to know about the involvement of Waqas in various terror blasts in India only after he was arrested,'' the source added. Nasir, who reportedly has links with human-trafficking gangs, used to grease the palms of officials guarding the border checkpost at Malda and smuggle people in and out of the country. Fugitive Bangladeshi national Noor has become a crucial link for the case as it was he, who during his stay in Zaheerabad of Medak district, introduced the now arrested Sohail Parvez Khan, a resident of Balapur, to Nasir to help the Pakistani settle in Hyderabad. Also, it was Parvez who helped Nasir and his wife get employment at the Unani hospital in Jalapally.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/hyderabad/HuJI-terrorist-Jabbar-roamed-freely-in-India/articleshow/48498142.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">HuJI terrorist Jabbar roamed freely in India</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/hyderabad/HuJI-terrorist-Jabbar-roamed-freely-in-India/articleshow/48498142.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terror Attack Bid Foiled in Assam, Terrorist Dead, Bomb Recovered</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/army-foils-bid-to-blow-up-rail-tracks-in-assam-1207190</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Assam</str>
    <str name="longitude">92.937574</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.200604</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Naveed is From Pakistan for Sure: Counter-Terror Chief to NDTV</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-naveed-is-from-pakistan-for-sure-counter-terror-chief-to-ndtv-1207001</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Captured Pak Terrorist Flown to Delhi by National Investigation Agency</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/captured-pak-terrorist-flown-to-delhi-by-national-investigation-agency-1206954</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Delhi</str>
    <str name="longitude">77.209021</str>
    <str name="lattitude">28.613939</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">India to Formally Request Pak for Information on Terrorist Naveed: Sources</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/india-makes-it-official-will-formally-request-pak-for-information-on-terrorist-naveed-1206408</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Bravehearts Who Caught Pakistani Terrorist Naveed to Get Shaurya Chakra</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/bravehearts-who-caught-pakistani-terrorist-naveed-to-get-shaurya-chakra-1206697</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Shaurya Chakra Recommended For Bravehearts Who Captured Terrorist Naveed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/shaurya-chakra-recommended-for-bravehearts-who-captured-terrorist-naveed-1206333</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Captured Pak Terrorist Naveed Interrogated by National Investigation Agency Chief</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/captured-pak-terrorist-naveed-interrogated-by-national-investigation-agency-chief-1206666</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">National Investigation Agency Chief to Question Captured Pakistani Terrorist Mohammed Naveed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/national-investigation-agency-chief-to-quiz-captured-pakistani-terrorist-mohammed-naveed-1206251</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pakistani Terrorist Naveed Sent to National Investigation Agency Custody for 14 Days</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pakistani-terrorist-naveed-sent-to-national-investigation-agency-custody-for-14-days-1206056</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Lashkar-e-Taiba is a terrorist organisation, not Pakistan: Kabir Khan</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//entertainment/hindi/bollywood/news/Lashkar-e-Taiba-is-a-terrorist-organisation-not-Pakistan-Kabir-Khan/articleshow/48423306.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">14-day police custody for Pakistani terrorist Naved</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/14-day-police-custody-for-Pakistani-terrorist-Naved/articleshow/48432369.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Investigators Reconstructing Events of Terrorist Naveed's Stay in Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/cheat-sheet/investigators-reconstructing-events-of-terrorist-naveeds-stay-in-kashmir-1205183</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kashmir</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.576171</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.778175</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Udhampur attack: JandK police arrest man who gave shelter to captured Pak terrorist Naved</str>
    <str name="body">SRINAGAR: JandK police have arrested a man who gave shelter to captured Pakistani terrorist Naved Usman, Times Now reported on Saturday. Naved Usman alias Qasim Khan of Faisalabad, captured three days ago, was on Saturday brought to the Kashmir Valley to identify those who helped him reach Udhampur where he was arrested, an official said. Usman, a member of the Lashkar-e-Taiba (LeT) terror outfit, was brought to the valley from Jammu region by road, an intelligence officer said. Usman was overpowered by villagers after he and a fellow Pakistani terrorist shot dead two Border Security Force (BSF) troopers on the Jammu-Srinagar highway in Udhampur district on August 5. The captured Pakistani is now in the custody of the National Investigation Agency (NIA). READ ALSO: A month after Ufa thaw, Islamabad ensures that peace lies in pieces How Naved stayed in JandK for 45 days before Udhampur terror attack JandK terror attack: Pak militant arrested alive, interrogation on BSF bravehearts: How martyred BSF jawans killed a terrorist, prevented mayhem While NIA officials reached here on Friday from Delhi, Usman has been brought to establish the route he used to reach Udhampur and to identify accomplices who facilitated his passage to Udhampur, the officer said. Usman is expected to identify the hideouts used by him after he crossed into Jammu and Kashmir's Kupwara district from Pakistan and also the other LeT cadres he met while planning the attack. The NIA has taken over Usman's interrogation to know more about the LeT network in Jammu and Kashmir and elsewhere in India. Usman is now reportedly lodged in an office of the Special Operations Group of the Jammu and Kashmir Police in Srinagar. (With inputs from agencies)</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Udhampur-attack-JK-police-arrest-man-who-gave-shelter-to-captured-Pak-terrorist-Naved/articleshow/48401358.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Udhampur</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.2479061</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.8262839</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Udhampur attack: JandK police arrest man who gave shelter to captured Pak terrorist Naved</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Udhampur-attack-JK-police-arrest-man-who-gave-shelter-to-captured-Pak-terrorist-Naved/articleshow/48401358.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Udhampur</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.2479061</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.8262839</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Student Turned Terrorist Dies in Pulwama Encounter</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/student-turned-terrorist-dies-in-pulwama-encounter-1204728</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pulwama</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.014382</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.981889</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">The Inside Story of Terrorist Naved's Interrogation</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/the-inside-story-of-terrorist-naveds-interrogation-1204774</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">This is the Home in Pakistan of Captured Terrorist Naveed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/this-is-the-home-in-pakistan-of-captured-terrorist-naved-1205007</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">MP Dhoot to reward villagers Rs 5 lakh for nabbing Pakistan terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">AURANGABAD: The Shiv Sena Rajya Sabha MP from Aurangabad, Rajkumar Dhoot, has announced a reward, worth Rs 5 lakh, for the two villagers from Udhampur, who overpowered an AK-47-wielding Pakistani terrorist. Usman Naved alias Kasim had sneaked in from across the border to kill Amarnath yatris and attack military targets. "In appreciation of the tremendous bravery and patriotism shown by the two young citizens, namely Rajesh Kumar and Rajesh Sharma, in capturing dreaded terrorist in Jammu area while putting their own lives at risk, I offer Rs 5 lakh to be shared between both of them," said the MP in a statement issued here on Thursday. Dhoot further said that his team would get in touch with the villagers in a few days to personally handover the cash prize. Naved had taken three residents of a border village in Udhampur, hostage after attacking a BSF bus on the Srinagar-Jammu national highway, near Udhampur. He asked the villagers to take him to a safe place where he could hide until he got the opportunity to cross over the border. In some time, Naved said that he was hungry and sat down to eat, unwittingly lowering his guard. Sensing an opportunity, Rajesh Kumar, one of the three villagers, grabbed him by the neck while another villager took away the terrorist's gun. The captured terrorist has said that he hailed from Faisalabad, Pakistan and had been on Indian soil for the past 12 days.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/MP-Dhoot-to-reward-villagers-Rs-5-lakh-for-nabbing-Pakistan-terrorist/articleshow/48383479.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Admission by captured terrorist Naved’s father blows Pak denial sky-high</str>
    <str name="body">ISLAMABAD/NEW DELHI: In an audacious re-run of the Ajmal Kasab episode after 26/11, Pakistan has disowned Lashkar-e-Taiba jihadi Mohammad Naved who was captured alive after carrying out a terror attack on a BSF bus. Pakistan foreign office spokesperson Syed Qazi Khalilullah dismissed as "baseless" Naved's admission about being a resident of Faisalabad. "We have repeatedly asked India to refrain from accusations," he said. "We have said many times that making immediate accusation on Pakistan is not correct. These things should be based on facts. We expect that whenever Pakistan is being accused of something, it shall be accompanied by concrete evidence." READ ALSO: Jihadis step up provocation, spread ops beyond Valley to grab eyeballs The exertions would have carried more credibility had it not been for the details provided by Naved of his Pakistani citizenship and, more importantly, the fact that Pakistan had engaged in similar falsehood the last time a jihadi was caught alive. A newspaper claimed that Naved's father in Pakistan, Mohammed Yakub, confirmed that the jihadi was his son before he abruptly discontinued the conversation saying Lashkar would come after him. "I'll be killed. The Lashkar is after us and the fauj (army) is after us," Yaqub told a newspaper when contacted on a phone number given to the interrogators by Naved. Identifying himself as the "unfortunate father" of the attacker, Yakub said, "You are calling from India. We'll be killed." He added, "The Lashkar is after us. They probably wanted him dead and not caught alive. Please spare him." On Thursday, Naved provided his interrogators with more details of his Pakistani citizenship, including the phone numbers of his brother Mohammad Nadeem and his cousin and brother-in-law Mohammad Tahir. READ ALSO: Naved will be taken to Udhampur encounter spot Immediately after his capture, Naved had said one of his brothers taught at Government College, Faisalabad, while another was engaged in the hosiery business. He also told his interrogators that he was launched in India by Lashkar handlers with the instruction to attack military targets and Amarnath yatris. When Ajmal Kasab was caught during the three-day carnage by LeT operatives in Mumbai in 2008, Pakistan brushed aside his acknowledgement about being a Pakistani national who had had been sent to Mumbai on a terror raid. In a stunning replay of Islamabad's anxiety to wash its hands of the 20-year-old who constitutes strong evidence of Pakistan's authorship of jihadi terror directed at India, newspaper reports in the neigbouring country said Naved did not figure in their citizens' database. "National Database and Registration Authority (NADRA) record shows Indian claims of an arrested person, Usman Khan (Mohammed Naved Yakub), originating from Pakistan are totally baseless," Pakistani officials were quoted as saying. In 2008, the official line on Kasab was exactly the same until an intrepid reporter from Pakistani news channel Geo travelled to his village in Faridkot to confirm the Indian claims. Following that report, Pakistan had no option but to acknowledge Kasab's nationality. Still, it refused to provide him any legal assistance, even refusing to claim his body after his execution. READ ALSO: 'Hardened jihadi' Naved changes versions, foxes interrogators Naved, along with another terrorist Noman alias Momin, fired at a BSF convoy on the highway at Simroli. BSF jawans retaliated killing Noman while Naved was later captured alive. The Naved story is turning out to be a replay, with Pakistan appearing to be desperate to distance itself from the young jihadi, a "smoking gun" in terms of his value as evidence of Pakistan's sponsorship of the terror campaign aimed against India. The story, the person and debates about his identity will be played out during the forthcoming NSA talks if the Pakistani authorities actually agree to come to India.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Admission-by-captured-terrorist-Naveds-father-blows-Pak-denial-sky-high/articleshow/48383853.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">MP Dhoot to reward villagers Rs 5 lakh for nabbing Pakistan terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/MP-Dhoot-to-reward-villagers-Rs-5-lakh-for-nabbing-Pakistan-terrorist/articleshow/48383479.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Admission by captured terrorist Naved’s father blows Pak denial sky-high</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Admission-by-captured-terrorist-Naveds-father-blows-Pak-denial-sky-high/articleshow/48383853.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naved Entered India 45 Days Ago, Trained by Lashkar: Sources</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/what-interrogators-know-about-pakistani-terrorist-mohammad-naved-ndtv-exclusive-1204482</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Lashkar, Pak Army Will Kill Me: Terrorist Naved's Father to Newspaper</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/ill-be-killed-says-father-of-captured-pakistan-terrorist-in-newspaper-interview-1204642</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Lashkar</str>
    <str name="longitude">78.15602875</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.19902992</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'Staring at Death, We Took a Chance': The Men Who Caught a Pak Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/staring-at-death-we-took-a-chance-the-men-who-caught-a-pak-terrorist-1204424</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naved 'Extremely Hardened', Keeps Smiling: Sources</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/cheat-sheet/pakistani-terrorist-interrogated-all-night-central-agencies-step-in-today-1204415</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Terrorist Naved Claims he 'Didn't Know' His Partner: Sources</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/cheat-sheet/pak-terrorist-naved-claims-he-didnt-know-his-partner-sources-1204605</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist who sneaked in across border captured</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-who-sneaked-in-across-border-captured/articleshow/48368076.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Kasab 2: Village defence men overpowered terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Kasab-2-Village-defence-men-overpowered-terrorist/articleshow/48368059.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-06T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">BSF bravehearts: How martyred BSF jawans killed a terrorist, prevented mayhem</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/BSF-bravehearts-How-martyred-BSF-jawans-killed-a-terrorist-prevented-mayhem/articleshow/48371781.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pakistani Terrorist Was Captured By Villagers He Took Hostage</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/pakistani-terrorist-was-captured-by-villagers-he-took-hostage-1204134</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Left for India 12 Days Ago, Says Pakistani Terrorist, Smiling After Capture</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/came-into-india-12-days-ago-says-pakistani-terrorist-smiling-after-capture-1204184</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Naved, Billed as 'Kasab II', Could Offer New Evidence of Pak Role</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-naved-billed-as-kasab-ii-could-offer-new-evidence-of-pak-role-1204277</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'It's Fun Doing This,' Says Captured Pakistani Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/its-fun-doing-this-says-captured-pakistani-terrorist-1204224</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Caught After Attack in Jammu's Udhampur is Pakistani, Say Police</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/3-soldiers-injured-after-terrorists-attack-their-convoy-in-jammus-udhampur-1203979</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu Udhampur</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Attack on BSF convoy in JandK's Udhampur: One terrorist caught alive, all hostages freed</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: One of the terrorists who attacked a BSF convoy in Udhampur on Wednesday morning has been caught alive and all the hostages have been freed. The security forces are conducting post-attack operations. The entire area has been cordoned off. Minister of state in PMO Jitendra Singh confirmed that one terrorist had been caught alive and the three hostages have been rescued. According to TV reports, the militant who has been caught alive has been identified as Usman. According to some TV reports, it was the hostages who misguided the terrorists to a police station. However, there is still no official confirmation of this. Earlier today, militants had attacked a convoy of BSF on the Jammu-Srinagar National Highway in Udhampur district killing two BSF jawans. Around eight personnel were injured in the attack. READ ALSO: Militants attack BSF convoy on JandK highway, 2 jawans and 1 ultra killed One terrorist was killed in the counterattack by the security forces. "Militants fired at a BSF convoy at Narsu Nallah situated between Udhampur town and Chenani town on the Jammu-Srinagar national highway today (Wednesday)," a senior police officer said. READ ALSO: Attack on BSF convoy in Udhampur a worrying development, Omar says Security forces check the body of a suspected rebel after a gunbattle on the Jammu- Srinagar highway at Narsoo Nallah, near Udhampur. (AP photo)</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Attack-on-BSF-convoy-in-JKs-Udhampur-One-terrorist-caught-alive-all-hostages-freed/articleshow/48357677.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">JandK Udhampur</str>
    <str name="longitude">5.916666985</str>
    <str name="lattitude">36.45000076</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Attack on BSF convoy in JandK's Udhampur: One terrorist caught alive, all hostages freed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Attack-on-BSF-convoy-in-JKs-Udhampur-One-terrorist-caught-alive-all-hostages-freed/articleshow/48357677.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">JandK Udhampur</str>
    <str name="longitude">5.916666985</str>
    <str name="lattitude">36.45000076</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist caught alive: What we know about Kasab II</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-caught-alive-What-we-know-about-Kasab-II/articleshow/48358434.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">BTFK terrorist seeks security during transportation</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/BTFK-terrorist-seeks-security-during-transportation/articleshow/48313700.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-08-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">BTFK terrorist seeks security during transportation</str>
    <str name="body">UNKNOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/BTFK-terrorist-seeks-security-during-transportation/articleshow/48313700.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-30T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">He's no terrorist, we are all working people here, says Mahim neighbour</str>
    <str name="body">MUMBAI: The street outside Al Hussain housing society in Mahim seemed quieter for its residents on Tuesday afternoon. The society watchman held on firmly to the large black iron gate, warding off reporters who wanted to enter. He had strict instructions from the Memon family in flat number 21 not to let anyone in. Rahin Memon, Yakub's wife, her father and daughter, now all grown up and a graduate who would make any father proud, all stayed indoors. The media vans that descended within minutes stayed a respectable distance away. Few neighbours and college friends of Yakub who hung around simmered with anger at what they said was "clear injustice to an innocent man." Salim Khan, a businessman and local resident, said, "Why is no one asking why the customs officers are let off so easily? They are the ones who allowed the arms to land that allowed the blasts. We feel sad for the tragic loss of innocent lives, but why is there no death sentence for them, for their corruption. Was that not criminal conspiracy and lack of patriotism by public servants?" He said the death sentence is "very harsh" and said that just because his brother Tiger is absconding, he was paying for it. "What were the Mahim police doing when activity was allegedly going on in the house which is a stone's throw away? Did they not know anything? He is no terrorist. We are all professional working people here in Mahim." Rahin, inconsolable last week after learning about the July 30 execution date, had a prayer on her lips and on her phone. "Allah knows every single tear you've shed for those you love. He knows the number of times your heart sank out of sadness and grief and undoubtedly. He heard every single 'Ya Allah' that escaped your quivering lips. Never for a moment lose hope in Him, cry to Him for as long as you need, for He is the only one who can turn your tears of sadness into ones of absolute bliss." Yakub, special PP Ujjwal Nikam however recalled, never mixed with other accused. "Others also avoided talking to him, because there was an impression among them that the Memons had betrayed them by having left the country before the blasts, after chalking out all plans for the blasts. Police would be very vigilent in court when the family was present," said Nikam adding that "Yakub would take all notes of court proceedings since he was most educated. While all other accused would joke around even with me, Yakub never did."</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/mumbai/Hes-no-terrorist-we-are-all-working-people-here-says-Mahim-neighbour/articleshow/48274303.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-30T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">He's no terrorist, we are all working people here, says Mahim neighbour</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/mumbai/Hes-no-terrorist-we-are-all-working-people-here-says-Mahim-neighbour/articleshow/48274303.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">My Name is Yakub Memon. I am Not a Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/my-name-is-yakub-memon-i-am-not-a-terrorist-1201264</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Residents hold candle march for Gurdaspur terrorist attack victims</str>
    <str name="body">LUDHIANA: A candle march was carried out on Monday by city residents to condemn the terrorist attack in Gurdaspur where seven people, including four policemen, were killed. They also raised slogans against Pakistan. Sukhminder Singh, of Asian Club, said: We are still living under threat. There has been no end to the fear of terrorism in the state. People were attacked in Gurdaspur but it has affected us all. No one throughout the state feels safe. Which ever group is responsible for these attack should be taken seriously by the government and they should be punished for this. Nothing is more important than innocent people's lives." "Return of terrorism in Punjab has shocked everyone, whether he is from Gurdaspur or not. In the age when politicians are always talking about peace and unity, there has been no improvement and common people are paying for it. We are now scared of moving out as you may never know that who could be a terrorist." said Chandrakant Chadda, a participant in the march.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/Residents-hold-candle-march-for-Gurdaspur-terrorist-attack-victims/articleshow/48244788.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Gurdaspur</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.32933807</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.96602058</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Security tightened in Kanpur after terrorist attack in Gurdaspur</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/kanpur/Security-tightened-in-Kanpur-after-terrorist-attack-in-Gurdaspur/articleshow/48243955.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Kanpur</str>
    <str name="longitude">80.41644287</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.27222061</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">HP on high alert after terrorist attack in Punjab</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/HP-on-high-alert-after-terrorist-attack-in-Punjab/articleshow/48244785.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">HP on high alert after terrorist attack in Punjab</str>
    <str name="body">SHIMLA: High alert has been sounded in Himachal Pradesh following terror attack at Dinanager town of Gurdaspur district in neighbouring Punjab. Entire border has been sealed and strict checking of vehicles is being ensured at all entry points. Security of dams, religious and tourist places has been increased. While state DGP Sanjay Kumar reviewed security arrangements following Monday's terror attack, chief minister Virbhadra Singh has appealed to people to report any suspicious activity to police immediately. Himachal Pradesh IGP (administration) Zahur H Zaidi said that state police have taken required steps to prevent spill over all such incidents in the bordering areas of Himachal Pradesh. He said that all police establishments have been directed to keep armed personnel ready and be prepared for deployment at the shortest possible time at all border checkposts. He said that special attention is being paid to movement of people into the state wearing Army and police uniforms. "In this regard, district SPs have been directed to coordinate with local Army authorities. Special vigil has also been put in place at vital installations, important religious establishments, bus stands and other places where large public congregations are expected throughout the state," he said. Zaidi said that special patrolling on railway tracks to check for explosives and improvised explosives has been started. Chief minister Virbhadra Singh said that such "cowardly and inhumane" activities by terrorists won't be tolerated. "This is an attack on the nation and those responsible would be dealt with according to law," he added. State DGP Sanjay Kumar said that state security agencies were keeping strict vigil at all public places and religious places. With major hydropower projects in place and crowded tourist and religious destinations, Himachal Pradesh had witnessed terror attack in the past when on August 3, 1998, terrorists killed 35 people in two incidents at Kalaban and Satrundi areas.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/HP-on-high-alert-after-terrorist-attack-in-Punjab/articleshow/48244785.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Residents hold candle march for Gurdaspur terrorist attack victims</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/Residents-hold-candle-march-for-Gurdaspur-terrorist-attack-victims/articleshow/48244788.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Gurdaspur</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.32933807</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.96602058</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UN Meets in Spain to Tackle 'Foreign Terrorist Fighters'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/un-meets-in-spain-to-tackle-foreign-terrorist-fighters-1200894</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Spain</str>
    <str name="longitude">-3.74922</str>
    <str name="lattitude">40.46366700000001</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist Attacks Will be Handled With Iron Hand: Arun Jaitley</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/terrorist-attacks-will-be-handled-with-iron-hand-arun-jaitley-1201132</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab's Dinangar town</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjabs-Dinangar-town/articleshow/48231198.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab Dinangar</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.47270203</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.13484955</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: No hostage situation yet, Rijiju says</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-No-hostage-situation-yet-Rijiju-says/articleshow/48232520.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: Army units arrive at spot</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-Army-units-arrive-at-spot/articleshow/48231686.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: Rajnath instructs BSF to 'step up vigil on India-Pak border</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-Rajnath-instructs-BSF-to-step-up-vigil-on-India-Pak-border/articleshow/48231717.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: Rajnath speaks to Badal on Gurudaspur</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-Rajnath-speaks-to-Badal-on-Gurudaspur/articleshow/48231811.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab may have been to target Amarnath yatris, says defence expert</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-may-have-been-to-target-Amarnath-yatris-says-defence-expert/articleshow/48231885.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: No hostage situation yet, Rijiju says</str>
    <str name="body">CHANDIGARH:Minister of state for home affairs Kiren Rijiju on Monday said no hostage situation in the Gurdaspur attack has been reported so far. "The attack is serious. I can't give any details as the operation is still going on. No hostage situation has been reported so far," he said. Meanwhile, ANI reporter on the ground has said that no exchange of gunfire has taken place for the past 10 minutes. One militant has been killed while a Punjab Special Service Group (SSG) jawan has sustained injuries in the ongoing operations. The death toll in the attack has now risen to eight, including six civilians and two home guards. Four civilians have also sustained injuries. The gun battle between the security forces and alleged terrorists ensued after the latter opened fire on the police station and a bus.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-No-hostage-situation-yet-Rijiju-says/articleshow/48232520.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-27T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terrorist attack in Punjab: Rajnath instructs BSF to 'step up vigil on India-Pak border</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: Union home minister Rajnath Singh on Monday instructed Border Security Force (BSF) DG, DK Pathak to step up the vigil along the India-Pakistan border in the wake of the attack in Gurdaspur. "Spoke to DG BSF Shri DK Pathak and instructed him to step up the vigil on India-Pakistan border in the wake of attack in Gurudaspur," Rajnath tweeted. READ ALSO: Suspected terror attack in Gurdaspur injures seven persons Rajnath had earlier said spoken to Punjab CM Prakash Singh Badal, home secretary LC Goyal and NSA Ajit K Doval regarding the suspected terror attack. Meanwhile, the death toll in the attack has risen to five following the death of two police home guards during the operations. The gun battle between security forces and alleged terrorists ensued after the latter opened fire on the police station and a bus. READ ALSO: Nine killed in suspected terror attack in Punjab's Gurdaspur Five bombs have also been recovered from the Dina Nagar-Pathankot railway track.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Terrorist-attack-in-Punjab-Rajnath-instructs-BSF-to-step-up-vigil-on-India-Pak-border/articleshow/48231717.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Punjab</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.341218</str>
    <str name="lattitude">31.147131</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Could Twitter Stop the Next Terrorist Attack?</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://gadgets.ndtv.com/social-networking/features/could-twitter-stop-the-next-terrorist-attack-719432</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Dedicated anti-terrorist squad for Port City soon</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/visakhapatnam/Dedicated-anti-terrorist-squad-for-Port-City-soon/articleshow/48196548.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Port City</str>
    <str name="longitude">-3.827980042</str>
    <str name="lattitude">51.60359955</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-23T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">2 Swedes Arrested on Syria Terrorist Crime Suspicion</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/2-swedes-arrested-on-syria-terrorist-crime-suspicion-784557</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Syria</str>
    <str name="longitude">38.996815</str>
    <str name="lattitude">34.802075</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">He’s no terrorist, we are all working people here, says Yakub Memon's Mahim neighbour</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/mumbai/Hes-no-terrorist-we-are-all-working-people-here-says-Yakub-Memons-Mahim-neighbour/articleshow/48167298.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">He’s no terrorist, we are all working people here, says Yakub Memon's Mahim neighbour</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//bombay-times/Hes-no-terrorist-we-are-all-working-people-here-says-Yakub-Memons-Mahim-neighbour/articleshow/48167303.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UN Chief Slams Terrorist Bomb Attack in Baghdad</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/un-chief-slams-terrorist-bomb-attack-in-baghdad-782879</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Baghdad</str>
    <str name="longitude">44.361488</str>
    <str name="lattitude">33.312806</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pakistani Terrorist Who Beheaded Indian Jawan Killed in Jammu and Kashmir</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/man-who-beheaded-indian-soldier-killed-in-jammu-and-kashmir-782424</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">China Says Detained Tourists Were Watching Terrorist Propaganda</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/china-says-detained-tourists-were-watching-terrorist-propaganda-781942</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">China</str>
    <str name="longitude">120.6545022</str>
    <str name="lattitude">24.2225023</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Jail inmates find it hard to believe that ‘Sir’ is a terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">NAGPUR: His spotless white flowing kurta and benign demeanour belies that he was once a terrorist. Yakub Memon is a popular figure in Nagpur Central Jail. His congeniality with fellow inmates and guards is on display every year during Eid in the high security 'fasi yard' of the prison, where he has been incarcerated since the Bombay high court confirmed his death sentence pronounced by a Tada court. But the coming Eid may be his last if his curative petition before the Supreme Court is rejected. The warrant of the Tada court set July 30 as the date of his execution. Yakub, the younger brother of 1993 blasts mastermind Tiger Memon, who has been absconding, is humility personified. In jail, he has stayed away from controversies. A chartered accountant, he is a voracious reader and finished his masters in political science last year even as his hopes of escaping the death penalty almost vaporized after President Pranab Mukherjee rejected his mercy plea. Jail sources said Yakub went into a shell for some time after Afzal Guru was hanged in 2013 in the 2001 Parliament attack case. Yakub's zeal to help others was well-known inside the jail. His behaviour even left many wondering if he indeed had a role in the 1993 blasts, which killed 257 people and injured 713. "Many inmates call him 'sir'. Others address him as 'Yakub bhai'. Even the guards are courteous to him. Seldom does he get into arguments. He prefers silence to protesting if something irks him," said a jail source. "Many inmates consider him a mentor. Others look up to him as a teacher, who is full of wisdom." A source who has seen Yakub in the jail's administrative office recalled how the clerical staff approached him for suggestions and he would be ready with solutions. "Jail staff and inmates working in the office get up from their seats when Yakub walks in," said the source. Yakub's counsel Anil Gedam said his client often teaches English and other subjects to inmates and this was included in the mercy petition. "I found him to be humble whenever I met him," Gedam said. A former inmate, who saw the "soft-spoken" Yakub during Eid festivities, said that looking at him he "certainly did not feel that he could be a terrorist".</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/nagpur/Jail-inmates-find-it-hard-to-believe-that-Sir-is-a-terrorist/articleshow/48092663.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-16T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Jail inmates find it hard to believe that ‘Sir’ is a terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/nagpur/Jail-inmates-find-it-hard-to-believe-that-Sir-is-a-terrorist/articleshow/48092663.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-10T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pak Uses Terrorist Outfits as Proxies, Says US Army General</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/pak-uses-terrorist-outfits-as-proxies-says-us-army-general-779949</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Senate Bill Would Make Social Media Report 'Terrorist Activity'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-senate-bill-would-make-social-media-report-terrorist-activity-779583</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Maharashtra govt feels threat to LeT terrorist Jundal's life</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Maharashtra-govt-feels-threat-to-LeT-terrorist-Jundals-life/articleshow/47996655.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Maharashtra</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.713888</str>
    <str name="lattitude">19.75148</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-07-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Maharashtra govt feels threat to LeT terrorist Jundal's life</str>
    <str name="body">NEW DELHI: There is a threat of assassination of suspected top Lashkar-e-Toiba terrorist Abu Jundal, a key conspirator of the 26/11 Mumbai attacks, from 'rival groups' during his transportation from jail to court, the Maharashtra government feels. A trial court, which is hearing terror cases against Jundal, was informed of the Maharashtra government's apprehension by the National Investigation Agency (NIA) which has requested the court to expedite the proceedings and conduct the case proceedings through video conferencing so that Jundal is not required to travel from jail to court. The agency, in its plea, also said that because of the threat to Jundal alias Sayed Zabiuddin Ansari, who is presently lodged in Arthur Road jail in Mumbai, he could not be produced before the city court on several occasions despite issuance of production warrants against him. The application for video conferencing was filed before District Judge Amar Nath who is hearing a case in which Jundal was chargesheeted for offences punishable under the IPC and Unlawful Activities (Prevention) Act for allegedly attempting to recruit men through Internet for banned outfit, Lashkar-e-Toiba, and conspiring to carry out terror activities in India. NIA had chargesheeted Jundal for allegedly conspiring to carry out terror activities in India, including the 26/11 Mumbai terror attacks and 2006 Aurangabad arms haul case. In the plea, NIA also referred to a resolution passed by the Maharashtra government in May 2013 by which Jundal was excluded from personal appearances in court due to threats of possible bids of assassination or abduction. Referring to the resolution, NIA, in its plea, said, "exclude the personal appearance of the accused Sayed Zabiuddin Ansari....after taking into consideration the request of the Commissioner of Police, Mumbai to exclude the above-mentioned accused person from personal appearance before court in various cases registered against him due to possibility of assassination bid on the life of accused by rival group or a bid to abduct." The agency also told the court that the resolution was challenged by Jundal before Bombay High Court, but his plea was dismissed. "By virtue of order passed by state government... and order of divisional bench of Bombay High Court... the jail authority is not producing accused Sayed Zabiuddin Ansari... inspite of the production warrant issued by this court directing jail authority to produce the accused before him to answer the charges levelled," the NIA application said. The court has issued notice to Jundal's counsel MS Khan and sought his reply on NIA's plea. The case is at the stage of arguments on framing of charges in the case. The court will hear arguments on NIA's plea on July 17. Jundal is considered to be one of the masterminds of the 26/11 Mumbai terror attacks in which the lone arrested accused Ajmal Kasab was convicted and hanged. Jundal was reportedly directing the terrorists during the attacks from the 'control room' in Pak-occupied Kashmir.</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Maharashtra-govt-feels-threat-to-LeT-terrorist-Jundals-life/articleshow/47996655.cms?</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Maharashtra</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.713888</str>
    <str name="lattitude">19.75148</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-30T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">French Prosecutor Confirms Terrorist Motive, Islamic State Link to Factory Beheading</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/french-prosecutor-confirms-terrorist-motive-islamic-state-link-to-factory-beheading-776762</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-30T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Mohit Raina as a terrorist?</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//tv/news/hindi/Mohit-Raina-as-a-terrorist/articleshow/47866544.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-30T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Mohit Raina as a terrorist in 'Diya Aur Baati Hum'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//television-highlights/Mohit-Raina-as-a-terrorist-in-Diya-Aur-Baati-Hum/articleshow/47875207.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-25T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Designates Names Taliban Captive 'Global Terrorist'</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-designates-names-taliban-captive-global-terrorist-774998</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Alka Kaushal returns as a terrorist to TV show</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//tv/news/hindi/Alka-Kaushal-returns-as-a-terrorist-to-TV-show/articleshow/47735626.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Why isn’t the church attacker called a terrorist?</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/Why-isnt-the-church-attacker-called-a-terrorist/articleshow/47741988.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-19T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Saibaba is member of banned terrorist outfit: IG Kadam</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/nagpur/Saibaba-is-member-of-banned-terrorist-outfit-IG-Kadam/articleshow/47726621.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Saibaba</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.14472961</str>
    <str name="lattitude">18.67573929</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Strike on 'Al-Qaeda-Associated Terrorist' in Libya: Pentagon</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-strike-on-al-qaeda-associated-terrorist-in-libya-pentagon-771639</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'Twitter Terrorist' Woman Jailed for 3 Years</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/twitter-terrorist-woman-jailed-for-3-years-771046</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-12T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">AAP Punished for Defeating Modi, Minister Treated like Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/opinion/aap-punished-for-defeating-modi-minister-treated-like-terrorist-771014</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-03T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Defence Minister Parrikar's 'Terrorist-for-Terrorist' Remark Gave Pakistan a Handle: Omar Abdullah to NDTV</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/defence-minister-parrikars-terrorist-for-terrorist-remark-gave-pakistan-a-handle-omar-abdullah-said-768408</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-06-02T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">First Look: Riteish Deshmukh as Bangistan's Bumbling Terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://movies.ndtv.com/bollywood/first-look-riteish-deshmukh-as-bangistans-bumbling-terrorist-767948</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-29T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Kenyan Man Pleads Guilty in US to Supporting Terrorist Groups</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/kenyan-man-pleads-guilty-in-the-united-states-of-america-to-supporting-terrorist-groups-766892</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Islamic State, other terrorist organizations recruiting NRIs: NIA</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Islamic-State-other-terrorist-organizations-recruiting-NRIs-NIA/articleshow/47401885.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-23T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Defence Minister Manohar Parrikar's 'Terrorist' Comment Insulted Military: Congress</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/defence-minister-manohar-parrikars-terrorist-comment-insulted-military-congress-765513</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Musharraf gloats over Kargil, 2014 Sikh terrorist photo in Pak nails lie</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/Musharraf-gloats-over-Kargil-2014-Sikh-terrorist-photo-in-Pak-nails-lie/articleshow/47354046.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Kargil</str>
    <str name="longitude">76.09999847</str>
    <str name="lattitude">34.56999969</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">2014 photo of Khalistan terrorist nails Pak lie</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/2014-photo-of-Khalistan-terrorist-nails-Pak-lie/articleshow/47350055.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Khalistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">47.96666718</str>
    <str name="lattitude">29.29999924</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-18T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UK's Most Wanted Female Terrorist Responsible For 400 Deaths: Reports</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/uks-most-wanted-female-terrorist-responsible-for-400-deaths-reports-764088</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Dzhokhar could be 1st terrorist to be executed in US since 911</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/us/Dzhokhar-could-be-1st-terrorist-to-be-executed-in-US-since-911/articleshow/47314420.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Indian Mujahideen Terrorist Flees Nepal Jail after Earthquake, Arrested From Uttar Pradesh</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/indian-mujahideen-terrorist-flees-nepal-jail-after-earthquake-arrested-from-uttar-pradesh-762312</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Uttar Pradesh</str>
    <str name="longitude">80.9461592</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.8467088</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-11T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Teenage suspected terrorist appears in Australian court</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/rest-of-world/Teenage-suspected-terrorist-appears-in-Australian-court/articleshow/47228213.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-05-01T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Attack on Prof Joseph a ‘terrorist act’, 13 convicted</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/kochi/Attack-on-Prof-Joseph-a-terrorist-act-13-convicted/articleshow/47115531.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-04-22T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">‘Terrorist’ wife taught bomb-making</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Terrorist-wife-taught-bomb-making/articleshow/47004003.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-04-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Top JMB terrorist held in Pakur</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/ranchi/Top-JMB-terrorist-held-in-Pakur/articleshow/46979784.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakur</str>
    <str name="longitude">87.81809998</str>
    <str name="lattitude">24.63850021</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-04-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Top JMB terrorist held in Pakur</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Top-JMB-terrorist-held-in-Pakur/articleshow/46981627.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakur</str>
    <str name="longitude">87.81809998</str>
    <str name="lattitude">24.63850021</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-04-08T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Kenya Freezes Key Money Transfers to Somalia Over Suspected Terrorist Links</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/kenya-freezes-key-money-transfers-to-somalia-over-suspected-terrorist-links-753328</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Kenya</str>
    <str name="longitude">37.906193</str>
    <str name="lattitude">-0.023559</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-04-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Terror note found on slain terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/delhi/Terror-note-found-on-slain-terrorist/articleshow/46830997.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-03-26T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Tunisia Arrests 23 in 'Terrorist Cell' Over Museum Attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/23-suspects-arrested-over-tunis-museum-attack-najem-gharsalli-749804</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Tunisia</str>
    <str name="longitude">9.245259285</str>
    <str name="lattitude">34.33528519</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-03-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Tainan KMT city councilors label mayor a terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">Chinese Nationalist Party (KMT) Tainan city councilors yesterday panned the city government’s removal of Chiang Kai-shek (蔣介石) statues from 14 junior-high and elementary schools in the municipality on Saturday, branding Tainan Mayor William Lai (賴清德) a “terrorist” and calling him “Emperor Lai.” KMT city councilors Lu Kun-fu (盧崑福), Wang Chia-chen (王家貞) and Tsai Shu-hui (蔡淑惠) said at a news conference in Tainan that the removal was arbitrarily executed without regard or respect for the schools’ autonomy, adding that Lai’s decision fostered further conflict between members of the pan-green and pan-blue camps. Having the statues wrapped in white cloth prior to removal made them resemble mummies, the councilors said, comparing Lai to the extremist Islamic State group, which has destroyed historical artifacts in Iraq. The city councilors called the operation “too secretive,” as the schools were not notified of the removals in advance. In response, Lai said the decision to remove the statues was not made on a whim, as it was announced on Feb. 28 while he was attending a memorial event to mark the 228 Incident. The statues were removed in the interests of transitional justice, Lai said, adding that schools are intended to be places to pass knowledge on to students. “Schools should not be places promoting political adoration, especially the adoration of Chiang,” Lai said. The removals were conducted over the weekend to minimize class disruptions, he said, adding that the workers wrapped the statues to protect them from damage. Opposing opinions are inevitable when a mayor decides to do something, he said, adding that he would gladly listen if such opinions were constructive, but that he would not be baited by aggressive commentary seeking to mislead the public. Separately yesterday, in response to a question posed by Taiwan Solidarity Union Legislator Lai Chen-chang (賴振昌), Minister of Culture Hung Meng-chi (洪孟啟) said that each statue has its own history, and he urged the nation to refrain from thinking politically about the statues. When Lai Chen-chang further inquired as to whether the presence of Chiang’s statues in school campuses was itself a political consideration, Hung said that “has its own historical background.”</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/taiwan/archives/2015/03/24/2003614292</str>
    <str name="source">taiwan</str>
    <str name="location">Tainan</str>
    <str name="longitude">120.2268758</str>
    <str name="lattitude">22.9998999</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-03-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">UN Chief Ban Ki-Moon Condemns 'Terrorist Attacks' at Yemen Mosques</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/un-chief-ban-ki-moon-condemns-terrorist-attacks-at-yemen-mosques-748407</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Yemen Mosques</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-03-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Kathua police station attack: 3 security personnel, 1 terrorist killed</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Kathua-police-station-attack-3-security-personnel-1-terrorist-killed/articleshow/46629462.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Kathua</str>
    <str name="longitude">75.51439667</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.37870026</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-03-10T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">'Eco-Terrorist' Threat to Poison New Zealand Baby Formula</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/eco-terrorist-threat-to-poison-new-zealand-baby-formula-745449</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Poison New Zealand Baby Formula</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Police Warn of Terrorist Attack Ahead of Bundesliga Match</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://sports.ndtv.com/article/238296</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-28T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Egypt Court Declares Hamas 'Terrorist' Group</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/egypt-court-declares-hamas-terrorist-group-743299</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Egypt</str>
    <str name="longitude">30.802498</str>
    <str name="lattitude">26.820553</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-21T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">5 Pak intruders slip into India, 1 'trained as terrorist' caught</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/5-Pak-intruders-slip-into-India-1-trained-as-terrorist-caught/articleshow/46319106.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">India</str>
    <str name="longitude">79.45809174</str>
    <str name="lattitude">23.40601158</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">British teen convicted of terrorist plan to behead soldier</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/uk/British-teen-convicted-of-terrorist-plan-to-behead-soldier/articleshow/46306859.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-18T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Embassy in Beijing issues safety alert to Japanese after media report getting terrorist attack info</str>
    <str name="body">The Japanese Embassy in Beijing is warning Japanese nationals living in China of possible terrorist attacks in public locations during the seven-day holidays that started Wednesday in conjunction with the Lunar New Year. The safety alert was issued to Japanese residents in China via ...</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2015/02/18/national/embassy-beijing-issues-safety-alert-japanese-media-report-getting-terrorist-attack-info/</str>
    <str name="source">japantimes</str>
    <str name="location">Beijing</str>
    <str name="longitude">116.407395</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.904211</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Manhunt under way after Copenhagen shootings; PM calls it a terrorist attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/europe/Manhunt-under-way-after-Copenhagen-shootings-PM-calls-it-a-terrorist-attack/articleshow/46249440.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Copenhagen</str>
    <str name="longitude">12.568337</str>
    <str name="lattitude">55.676097</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-14T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Media total up the targets for terrorist attacks</str>
    <str name="body">The 67-second video on YouTube opens with a black slate that reads, “A Message to Japan.” The video then shows a kneeling journalist, Kenji Goto, clad in an orange outfit. Behind him, flaunting a knife, is the masked executioner from the Islamic State group ...</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2015/02/14/national/media-national/media-total-targets-terrorist-attacks/</str>
    <str name="source">japantimes</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-07T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">US Charges 6 Over Iraq-Syria 'Terrorist' Links</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-charges-6-over-iraq-syria-terrorist-links-737666</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">US</str>
    <str name="longitude">-98.95733643</str>
    <str name="lattitude">39.44325638</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-02-05T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">NY court fixes pre-trial hearing of suit seeking ‘terrorist’ tag for RSS</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//city/chandigarh/NY-court-fixes-pre-trial-hearing-of-suit-seeking-terrorist-tag-for-RSS/articleshow/46128593.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-24T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">I Don't Think Everyone in Pakistan is a Terrorist: Rajnath Singh</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/i-dont-think-everyone-in-pakistan-is-a-terrorist-rajnath-singh-731825</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-20T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Tell Pakistan there is no good terrorist, India urges UK</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//india/Tell-Pakistan-there-is-no-good-terrorist-India-urges-UK/articleshow/45948026.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Pakistan Hangs Terrorist, 20th Execution Since Moratorium Lifted</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/pakistan-hangs-terrorist-20th-execution-since-moratorium-lifted-728526</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-17T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Nine killed in terrorist attack in Mali</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//world/rest-of-world/Nine-killed-in-terrorist-attack-in-Mali/articleshow/45917974.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">Mali</str>
    <str name="longitude">-3.996166</str>
    <str name="lattitude">17.570692</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-15T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Jammu on High Alert in Wake of Inputs of Terrorist Attack</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/india-news/jammu-on-high-alert-in-wake-of-inputs-of-terrorist-attack-727836</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Jammu</str>
    <str name="longitude">74.857654</str>
    <str name="lattitude">32.721782</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-13T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Mullah Fazlullah, Taliban Chief Who Scripted Pakistan School Massacre, Branded Global Terrorist by US</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://www.ndtv.com/world-news/mullah-fazlullah-taliban-chief-who-scripted-pakistan-school-massacre-branded-global-terrorist-by-us-726890</str>
    <str name="source">ndtv</str>
    <str name="location">Pakistan</str>
    <str name="longitude">69.345116</str>
    <str name="lattitude">30.375321</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-09T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">I am Shafqat Amanat Ali Khan and I am not a terrorist</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//entertainment/hindi/music/news/I-am-Shafqat-Amanat-Ali-Khan-and-I-am-not-a-terrorist/articleshow/45808833.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
  <doc>
    <date name="date">2015-01-01T00:00:00Z</date>
    <str name="headline">Dev turns terrorist!</str>
    <str name="body">UNKOWN</str>
    <str name="link">http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com//entertainment/bengali/movies/news/Dev-turns-terrorist/articleshow/45714877.cms</str>
    <str name="source">toi</str>
    <str name="location">unknown</str>
    <str name="longitude">unknown</str>
    <str name="lattitude">unknown</str></doc>
</result>
</response>
